'London.
The city of the rich.'
'For many, living here
is akin to living in paradise.'
'But like every other city,
there are some parts in the city'
'where only the unfortunate live.'
'My little house in Southall
was literally a jail for me.'
'I'd feel so suffocated over there.'
'I wanted to break free
of that prison.'
'Little did I know'
'that there prisons
of various kinds.'
Sonia, eat a 'paratha'
before you leave.
Mom, I'm already late.
I'll eat with Kabir.
Dear, don't ever do that.
Never go without eating
after you talk about food.
It's inauspicious.
Please. Don't say
these superstitious things.
Sonia makes her own luck.
So chill.
Jyoti, you're barking
at the wrong tree.
This girl is hopeless.
I'm sorry, dad. But living here
feels so hopeless.
It never feels like
we are living in London.
Bloody Southall.
- Oh really?
Why don't you live in Knightsbridge?
We gave you whatever we had.
She's an ungrateful daughter.
Dad, don't start now.
I'm just saying
I won't spend my life in...
What the hell!
Why am I even explaining it to you?
'I'd pinned all my hopes
to Kabir.'
'He had an audition scheduled
with a major music company.'
Hi. Can I have my tulips?
'If Kabir bags this contract'
'everything will be fine.
- Thank you.
'This was the only hope
that kept both of us going.'
Look at that.
What the hell!
How did that happen?
They say, when God gives you,
He gives you abundantly.
I was practising the whole night
and then I got too tired,
I left the guitar on the couch
and as usual
the roof started leaking.
In the morning, I noticed
the wood had blackened.
Damn! What will we do now?
Nothing. We wait.
For the next year.
Maybe dreams are fulfilled...
- No way, Kabir.
This is not only your dream,
but mine too.
We can't get out of here
till you achieve fame.
We'll be trapped in Southall
for good.
Do you think I like it here?
I hate this place more than you do.
But we don't have another option.
Baby, you don't worry.
Focus on your performance.
Leave the rest to me.
Okay?
Sonia! Early in the morning!
Either, you've landed in trouble
or you're about to start one.
Shut your mouth
or you'll be in trouble.
Fine! Tell me, what's the issue?
I have to open the restaurant.
I'm not free.
Pabbi, I need 500 pounds urgently.
Please help me.
500 quid.
Had I got that kind of money,
would I be working at this joint?
Pabbi, only you can help me now.
I'm desperate.
There is one way.
No, Pabbi, I won't do anything
like that.
Gosh! You decent people
and your inhibitions!
You don't want to be desperate,
you don't want to cut corners.
Yet you won't hesitate
to take ill-gotten gains.
You want Pabbi to take
all the risk
and you just want to enjoy.
Since you call me your friend,
here's my offer.
All you have to do is
deliver a package
and get paid for it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
The walls suffocate you
and you don't even
want to open the door.
Strange!
Okay, fine.
But just one time.
Wait, I'll get the packet.
Your package.
Come in.
No, no
I'd rather stay here.
My money?
For f**k's sake,
I'm not gonna hand over that
sort of money at the doorstep.
Anyway, I need to inspect
the merchandise.
So either come in or
take the f**king package and go.
I'll come. - Officer Smith.
- Who is this?
You've been asking around
for an Indian drug runner.
Well, I overheard a conversation
at my restaurant.
Eyes on the suspect!
Tell uniform that
we have a bit of tangle!
'Ladies, follow me.'
'You all have your assignment work
for his week.'
'Make yourself useful
and productive.'
'The only way of getting out
of here early'
'is to make yourself productive'
'to a society that believes
that you're completely useless.'
Shonda wants to lay.
Sonia, you have the t**t.
that is a very little use
over here in the next 14 years.
Shonda wants to make you
her first and her best.
You'll be a queen.
What have you got to lose?
Looks like we need to teach
this Indian b***h some prison rules.
B***h!
B***h! Get her!
B***h! B***h!
Get her! B***h!
Get her off!
Get her off! Get her off!
Get her off, you b***h!
All right, just back off!
Someone, call an ambulance.
Relax, you'll be fine.
When you came in,
there was blood everywhere.
But the doctors have
done a good job.
I'm in no hurry.
I have nowhere to go.
But I have something that
will put you in a better mood.
I've got someone here to see you.
I think you're gonna
want to see him.
Better than any medicine.
Red tulips.
Thank you.
My expert girlfriend says
red is for everlasting love.
She is a tulip expert.
Then you should've brought
the yellow one.
It suits my situation.
Because yellow is for hopeless love.
I haven't given up hopes yet.
You shouldn't give up either.
If you abandon hopes,
then you can't fight
the circumstances.
Hopes
I'll be spending 14 years
in prison,
how can I have any hopes?
You know we can appeal
for an early release.
I wish I could share
your optimism.
Anyway, forget about it.
Tell me about my family.
Are my parents
still angry with me?
They didn't come to meet me once.
They've forgiven you,
but maintaining relations with you
can affect your sisters.
They have to get married.
Since their sister is in jail,
that can harm their reputation.
They are right.
I didn't think about them.
So why would they think about me?
It was my life.
I lived my life on my own terms.
Life has brought me
at this juncture
and I don't blame anyone for it.
No one else is responsible.
Not even you.
Why are you waiting for me?
Are you crazy?
Kabir, you should leave
before my unfortunate life
makes your life bleak.
You're the light of my life, Sonia.
How can you bring darkness?
Don't be stupid.
Will you spend your life in dark
for this light?
My life has been ruined,
but why ruin yours?
Both of us wanted to
break free of Southall.
I couldn't get out,
but you still can.
Why do you want to live in
prison like me?
For my sake, Kabir.
You won't see me again.
Go away.
- I don't...
Been more than ten minutes, buddy.
Your time's up, I'm afraid.
It's a damn operation theatre.
Why am I brought here?
We'll have to close this,
so we thought we'd bring
portable x-ray machine to you.
Don't worry,
doctor will be here soon.
Hello. Hello.
Shonda sent you here, didn't she?
If she wants to kill me,
she should attack openly.
The day we want to kill you,
we'll do so without any permission.
Right now, I am here to save you.
I trade in lives.
My name is Kaya.
Are you a lawyer?
Did Kabir send you?
- Shut up and listen.
My company provides a
special service to our rich clients.
I trade in secrets.
This is a modern age weapon.
These days no one attacks openly.
If you want to finish off anyone,
just find out all his secrets.
Persuade, purchase, punish,
secrets. Secrets are very powerful.
We trade in secrets.
Traders of secrets.
Governments,
politicians, multinationals.
All of them need our services
every now and then.
But secrets aren't easily available.
You have to extract them.
That's what my team does.
We always need girls
who can help us out.
Whatever happened to you in jail,
consider it to be an interview.
I'm here to tell you,
you are hired.
You hired me,
but you didn't tell me
my job profile.
What can women offer in
the world controlled by men
except their bodies?
Prostitution.
It's an age-old business, girl.
We just do it with style.
What if I refuse this offer?
If you go back to jail,
you won't live.
Even if you live,
what will be your
life after 14 years?
What I am offering you
is not a job?
It's a lifestyle.
Think about it.
What do I have to do?
You'll have to die.
What?
Sonia must die??
Friends, families, relatives.
You'll have to severe ties
with everyone.
Even small weakness
in this profession
can prove fatal.
No past, no connections,
no weaknesses.
You'll be given a new identity,
a new life.
But once you enter our world,
you won't be able
to return to your old life.
So think before you say anything.
You have 24 hours.
In case, you decide to join us,
send for Dr Murphy.
'From the confines of Southall,
I ended up in jail.'
'Now I've been given a chance'
'to get out of jail
and enter Kaya's prison.'
'I looked closely and didn't find
much of a difference in them.'
'But I realised Sonia's death
will give me lots of benefits.'
'My parents and sisters won't
need to be ashamed anymore.'
'Kabir will stop waiting for me.'
'He'll be able to begin
his life anew.'
'Maybe everyone benefits
if I accept Kaya's offer.'
Yes! The Indian prisoner.
She's escaped.
No, I don't know.
Yes, the police. Yes.
Okay. Thank you, thank you.
S**t hit the fan.
Chris Toms.
- It's good to see you.
And you, men!
Stand down, stand down.
What's happening?
It's a big operation.
Come on, we don't have time.
I need you to change.
Quickly. We don't have time.
Come on, guys.
Quick, quick, quick.
Come on, do it fast!
Come no, quickly.
It's her, right?
She was trying to escape from jail.
The car was found in a ravine
and then there was an explosion.
We've found two bodies.
That too completely burnt.
Why would she try to escape?
She had no friends.
Who will she run with?
Drugs Mafia often
try to save their people.
This is a big misunderstanding.
She had no connection
with any drug Mafia.
No one knows her better
than I do.
Whatever she did,
she did it for me.
What's a betrayal?
You're always betrayed by
someone whom you trust.
I'm not saying you
know anything about this, but...
surely...
The fact is
that your girlfriend
was caught with drugs.
She tried to escape jail
and she had planned it well.
I still can't believe it.
Till Sonia personally tells me,
I can't believe any of it.
Welcome to the facility.
Take a closer look at this place.
This place will
turn you into a weapon.
A weapon which can destroy anything
or any person for that matter.
But before you target others,
you must target yourself.
You have to torture yourself
so much
so that no one
tortures yourself.
That's the thing about
broken hearts.
The heart has to break
only once.
You had left this in jail.
Thank you.
Tear it.
What?
Sonia Khanna is in that picture.
You have to kill Sonia Khanna
and be reborn again,
we must perform
her last rites.
Come on.
You must die to be reborn again.
Never mind.
The day you tear this picture,
your life will begin.
Carrying burden of your death
It's not easy.
"You're my day
and I am night."
"I don't exist without you."
"Without you, I'm not even earth"
"In you lies my vast sky."
"It's an incomplete dream."
"Your passion rages in me."
"You're in every breath of mine."
"You're my peace."
"You're my intoxication."
"How can I forget you?"
"You are my love."
"You're my peace."
"You're my intoxication."
"How can I forget you?"
"You are my love."
Hello, Jim.
- Hello, ma'am.
Go and seduce him.
Come on, go ahead.
"I'm a body"
"and you are my shadow."
It's a simple task.
Take this package all the way down.
Don't let anybody stop you.
"You live in my memories."
"Please live"
It's not the dog in the fight,
it's the fight in the dog.
"You're my sympathiser."
"You speak my language."
"You're tears in my eyes."
"You're my peace."
"You're my intoxication."
"How can I forget you?"
"You are my love."
"You're my peace."
"You're my intoxication."
"How can I forget you?"
"You are my love."
To be the best in this business,
you must accept your reality.
Repeat after me, Sonia.
My job is to sell my body
in exchange of secrets.
That's it and nothing else.
You can't come to terms
with the truth.
How will you be able to
sell your body?
Say it.
Say it!
"You're my moon"
Your so-called death
has given Kabir a new lease of life.
"You burn in me."
"May I touch you?"
"You are in my heartbeat."
"We've separated from each other
like fire from smoke."
"You're the grief of my soul."
"You're my peace."
"You're my intoxication."
"How can I forget you?"
"You are my love."
"You're my peace."
"You're my intoxication."
"How can I forget you?"
"You are my love."
Something is fishy about
Foston Penitentiary.
In the last eight months,
many female convict disappeared
and when they were discovered
their bodies were
beyond recognition.
Look at her.
Elizabeth Andrews.
She was convicted eight months ago.
She got ten years in prison.
You already have so many cases.
Why worry about this?
Listen. She is Sukhit Yakub.
She was serving life imprisonment.
When she was going for her
appeal hearing, she had an accident.
Her body was found completely burnt.
Then comes Sonia.
Sonia suffered the same fate.
It's a strange coincidence.
All these cases are similar.
Women have been convicted with
long-term prison sentences
have untimely accidents.
They die in accidents
and their bodies
are beyond recognition.
Something is wrong.
I am sure.
Soaib, I am your elder brother,
so here's a piece of advice.
Stop this madness
and focus on your work.
Your suspension is over.
The department still remembers
how you were found drunk in
a row house during your duty hours.
Focus on your work.
Just do as you are told.
Pick up this and get out of here.
Sonia Khanna.
You're playing hide and seek
with the law.
But you'll be caught one day.
I'll bring you to book.
A small gift from our organisation
for your new life.
I often gawked at skyscrapers
from the streets.
Never in my life I imagined,
I'd be able to peek down
from a skyscraper.
You've just started
scaling heights.
You have a long way to go.
We can talk about this later.
First, let's celebrate
your birthday.
My birthday?
- Here.
You were born in New Castle
in 1995.
Here's your passport, credit card,
license.
All the documents.
You didn't complete your education.
Right now, you are a model
who works with
Virago Model Agency, Manchester.
This is your work agreement
and your bank accounts.
Memorise things about your new life.
What's my name?
- Pari.
Henceforth, you are Pari.
Thank you for all this.
Before you move in here,
we must get rid of the old tenant.
Does someone else live here?
- She used to live here.
It's her last day today.
Meet Maneka.
Her life was
no different than yours.
I got her out of jail and
gave her shot at a luxurious life.
She wasn't happy despite
all the luxuries.
She wanted freedom.
She joined hands with our enemies
to achieve freedom.
There's still time, go back.
This freedom is a mirage
Listen carefully, buddy.
Meet Abu Hamza al-Riyadhi.
He's come here to buy
weapons worth millions
for the Arabian government.
He is a seasoned player.
Official version says,
he's coming here buy
surface-to-air missile technology.
But actually, he's met Andrei Kobrov
from Russia before coming here.
Andrei is the biggest arms dealer
in Russia.
'This is a common practice
in our business.'
'A client often gets quotation
from two vendors'
'and then decides which deal
suits him better.'
'We don't want to lose this deal.'
'So it's important that'
'our deal should be
better than the Russian dealer.'
'One more thing.'
'He'll be accompanied by
Faisal Baghdadi.'
'Be wary of him.'
'He is very sharp
and can be dangerous.'
'Abu Hamza will fly to Glasgow
for two days in a private jet.'
Praise be to Allah.
'The regular air hostess
will fall ill suddenly'
'and you are her replacement.'
'We have to secure the Russian deal
before tomorrow's arms deal.'
'But you don't need to
worry about Hamza.'
'Indian women are his weakness.'
'He'll come to you willingly.'
Pari.
Mr Hamza is expecting you.
Hi.
I'd like to think
it is my charm
not the money
that brought you here.
I saw the money.
I'm yet to see the charm.
I like a woman
with a sense of humour.
We are going to enjoy this.
There's a packet
in the guest bedroom.
You'll know how to use it.
Please.
There's no greater joy than
seeing a pretty girl in your power.
I like to hear painful screams
of a woman more than
Please! No, no!
Ladies and gentlemen, there seems
to be a false alarm.
As you can see none of
the sprinklers have been set off.
And so there is no real
danger of fire.
We're very, very sorry about this.
If you'd please return
to your rooms,
try and get some sleep.
The wounds aren't deep or else
you'd need stitches.
And plastic surgery to hide
those stitches.
If you know what I mean.
- I know.
I wish I knew he'd turn out
to be such a brute.
These lines are so apt.
"These days"
"the truth is a dream."
"You can't recognise anyone."
"For there's a mask over
every face."
I've realised one truth
amid this life of deceit.
Sex is never just sex.
It is a deal.
I have high hopes from you, Pari.
You'll make a quick progress.
I'm glad that my training
helped you.
The management will be
very happy with you.
Or else Mr Black doesn't
invite anyone to meet him.
Who is Mr Black?
This company is owned by Mr Black.
All of us work for him.
But no one knows
who is Mr Black.
No one has seen him so far.
He issues orders
and we follow them.
You haven't seen him either.
Yes, I have not.
Mr Black knows about everything.
So we don't need to
tell him anything.
If he wants to say anything,
he sends us a message
through his lawyer.
We're going to the same lawyer
right now.
Rutherford.
Mr Black interacts
with only Rutherford.
All of us follow
Rutherford's instruction.
You'll hear many stories
about Mr Black.
You'll have to decide which ones
are true and which are fiction.
We steal secrets for him,
but he himself is
the biggest secret.
Something like that.
Thank you so much for coming, Kaya.
And hi.
- You're welcome.
Is there anything in particular
Mr Black wanted to talk about?
Oh, no.
Nothing like that really.
Just that he was, he was
really happy with the Abu Hamza job.
He wanted to thank you
and see the girl who did it.
You mean he can see me right now.
Yes, he can.
Mr Black is also very sorry
for the way you were treated
by Abu Hamza.
And he is very appreciative
as you still managed
to get the information for us.
He wants to thank you
with this.
Should you accept it
Mr Black believes that brave act
must be rewarded.
I'm sure, you agree, Ms Kaya.
Oh, yes. Yes, I do.
Absolutely.
I think Pari is
going to be our best.
The best we've ever had.
"This night is full
of intoxication."
"As you are not with me."
"Had you been with me"
"Had I seen you"
"I would've looked at you closely."
"I would've loved you closely."
"I would've gazed at you
to my heart's content."
"I would've asked you
from my destiny."
"I would've thought about it
in your presence."
"I would've taken a plunge."
"I would've taken you
into my arms."
"I would've asked you
from my destiny."
"You were like a wave."
"I would flow with you"
"You were akin to a town."
"I'd live in you."
"Without you, I have to city
and no home."
"Without you, my life
has come to a standstill."
"Without you, I don't know anything,
I don't exist."
"Yes, I am. Yes, I am!"
"I would've gazed at you
to my heart's content."
"I would've loved you closely."
Let's leave.
"I would've taken you
into my arms."
"I would've asked you
from my destiny."
Sonia! Sonia, stop!
- Please step back.
Sir, please.
- I know her! Sonia.
Sonia, what the hell is going on?
Who are these people?
Get back.
- Just shut up.
Do you know this man, Pari?
Pari? She is not Pari,
she is Sonia.
I have no idea who he is
and what he is talking about.
Sonia!
- Come on, sir...
You can fool the world, but not me.
Why are you doing this to me, Sonia?
Sonia!
Sonia, listen to me.
"My days are angry with me."
"And so are my nights
Without you"
"I feel restless."
"My heart sinks without you."
"Without you, I battle loneliness
and I live in infamy."
"Without you, I hear strange murmurs
and silence haunts me."
"Without you, desolation looms
and sadness rules my heart."
"Yes, there is. Yes, there is!"
"I would've gazed at you
to my heart's content."
"I would've loved you closely."
The first cruise at the Thames
departs at 10 am.
I'll wait for you there.
"I would've asked
you from my destiny."
"I would've thought about it
in your presence."
"I would've taken a plunge."
"I would've taken you
into my arms."
"I would've asked you
from my destiny."
I'm not that Sonia anymore
whom you once loved.
I work for a shadow organisation
which is so powerful
that it can change
governments overnight.
They offered me a deal.
They'll help me escape prison
and I'll work for them.
They ask me to meet many men
and I oblige.
Did you run away from jail
for this life?
Sonia was already dead
in everyone's eyes.
The sooner you realise this,
the better it is for you.
You don't fall in love
thinking about consequences.
If you love me so much
then please listen to me.
My life now belongs to them.
I can't even breathe
without their permission.
You're their slave, not me.
I haven't sold my feelings.
You do what you think is right.
I've dedicated my life
to loving you.
As long as I live,
I won't stop loving you.
These people help the notorious
criminals assume new identities.
But they can just easily
blow your cover.
They won't take much time
to get rid of you.
Even if they erase my life,
I won't let anyone slander my love.
Bonne série!
- Hi, James.
There is a package for you.
Hand-delivered.
Hand-delivered package?
Yes. It came a couple
of minutes ago.
Hello, Pari.
- You?
The pictures you're
holding right now
are from your morning walk.
You are very lucky,
I got them before Kaya did.
But how?
Don't think about how and why.
Think hard as you're
running out of time.
If you got these pictures
before Kaya did,
then why am I running out of time?
Whatever mails or reports Kaya
receive are put into an envelope
and the envelope bears a number.
A duplicate copy is
sent for archival.
Whenever an envelope
or a number is missing,
Kaya understands that
something is wrong
and she accesses the duplicate
copy immediately.
An hour.
You have an hour.
Later...
Kaya will get this.
You know what she is going to do?
I will also suffer Maneka's fate.
She'll kill me.
- No.
She'll kill your boyfriend.
Hello. - We don't have must time,
so please listen carefully.
Sonia.
- 'Just do as you are told.'
Get some cash, some clothes
and sneak out through the back-door.
Don't let the CCTV cameras
in the front shop see you.
What's going on?
Cover your face
as much as you can.
So wear a hoodie and your glasses.
Don't meet anyone no matter what.
Head straight to the tube station
from your place
and then meet me at King's Cross.
I'll pick you up
in an silver Audi.
We only have 35 minutes.
Quick! Get in!
And this was today morning?
- Yes.
You know where
this boy stays, Kristov, I assume.
Yes, I do.
- Good.
This boy cannot remain alive.
No one should know
what we do and how we do it.
Put him away
and do it in a way
that Pari never finds out.
I'm sorry, ma'am, but
it's a little bit late for that.
What do you mean?
- If you'll allow me.
What the f*** is she doing?
You know what she is doing.
Someone has warned her.
She is probably on her way
to one of the many airports already.
Trying to save her boyfriend.
You'll get them, won't you, Kristov?
Both of them.
- Yes, ma'am.
Where are we going?
- Do you trust me?
Yes, I do. - Please understand
whatever I've learned from them,
I'm using it now
so that both of us
can get out of London.
Both of us, right?
Because I'm not leaving alone.
Yes.
For me, there is no way out now.
I betrayed them by saving you
and death is
the only punishment for that.
What happened?
Do you think it's a joke?
I'm just thinking about
the strange games that fate plays.
There was time when
we wanted to break free of Southall.
Today, we're running away,
but it's not the way
we wanted to it be.
At least, we are together.
This is more than enough.
"Open the door to our dreams."
"Let rain of kindness fall on me."
"Let me meet again with myself,
let my heart beat again."
"Let me burn with passion,
inflame the love flame again."
"Once again a bit"
"Heal my wound again."
"Take away my pain again."
"Let there be love
in the air again."
"Heal my wound again."
"Take away my pain again."
"Let your love soothe me again."
Any information?
Pari and the artist have hired
a silver Audi.
License plate number is
LO 17 DQ7. - I see.
Right now, the car is parked
outside a small hotel
in village Helford.
You have to handle the rest.
So Javed is
a part of this conspiracy.
Kristov, there is an address
I need you to check out.
"I want to start my life again"
"from the moment we went
separate ways."
"Our love story has been
unfulfilled for ages."
"Our future dreams
are flowing as tears"
"They'll take us
to our destination."
"Heal my wound again."
"Take away my pain again."
"Let there be love
in the air again."
"Heal my wound again."
"Take away my pain again."
"Let your love soothe me again."
'I wanted Verna to meet you.'
I wanted to show her
that we take such
a good care of our girls.
These tulips are very beautiful.
Where did you get them from?
I know a florist
who arranges them for me.
You also have books on them.
I think you love tulips.
Yes.
Tulips.
Tulips! That's where she has gone.
What do you mean?
When someone wants to
fulfil her dreams,
she goes where her dreams are.
And that's where she is.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
Where did you say she's gone?
Holland.
That's where she is.
But Pari isn't a fool
who will go to an airport
with a fake passport.
She'll use the passport
outside the airport.
That is why a ferry terminal.
As she wants to go away
as far as possible
Kristov, you should take your men
and go to Harwich.
I can bet my life,
Pari is riding the ferry
to Hoek van Holland.
Yes, ma'am.
'Passengers travelling from
custom and immigration'
'are requested to approach Gate 5C
for boarding.'
'Passengers travelling from
custom and immigration'
'are requested to approach Gate 5C
for boarding.'
'Passengers travelling from
custom and immigration'
'are requested to approach Gate 5C
for boarding.'
Go. 'Passengers, may I have
your kind attention.'
'Passengers, may I have
Bloody hell.
They are here.
Where?
Kristov is in the immigration booth.
Don't react at all.
Keep in line and act normal.
Now?
Let me think.
We've been surrounded.
Let's try to go some other day.
Let's leave now.
Listen to me carefully.
There will be a bedlam
after 30 seconds.
Cross the immigration
and wait for me there.
I'm not leaving you.
Kabir, you've not been
trained at this.
I don't care,
I'm not leaving you.
We'll make it alive
only if you listen to me.
Or else both of us will die.
Fine.
She is here!
Hello, Pari.
Drop the gun.
Drag her to the facility.
If you think
we are torturing you
then you are wrong.
You've brought this on yourself.
But all this can stop.
You just have to tell us
where your boyfriend is
right now
and what you have told him
about our organisation.
F*** you.
F*** you, Kaya.
Where is your boyfriend?
What have you told him
about our organisation?
He knows nothing.
He knows nothing about you.
Don't involve him, Kaya.
You involved him in this.
We didn't do that.
You met him
and then tried to run away
with him.
It's all your fault.
Yes, it's my fault.
Then kill me.
But you won't get Kabir's address.
Next time when I ask you,
you won't be alive to say anything.
Where is Kabir?
You are lucky.
Your torture will end
because we don't answers
from you anymore.
I'd advise you
to reflect on what you have done.
Look, what you've done.
You killed your boyfriend.
You know where our super efficient
cop Javed found him?
Keukenhof,
a small village in Holland.
He was trying to buy a
house in front of the tulips fields.
He was killed by the girl
who showed him the tulips dreams.
If I had my way, I would've
killed you along with him.
But Mr Black thinks
we can still use your services.
Only he knows
what use you'll be to us.
"I'm alive in your eyes."
"I'm the complaint on your lips."
"I'm in your life."
"I'll be there when I'm gone."
"Whether you see me or not,"
"I'm always with you."
Kabir.
"Please hide me in your heartbeat."
Kabir!
- "I am"
"Your feeling"
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
I knew Kaya would resort to this.
You're lucky
that Mr Black stopped her on time.
Or else, you were going
to die for sure.
Kaya can't go against Mr Black.
Don't they say
Clouds that rain,
don't bring thunder.
But one thing is sure.
Kaya won't let you live in peace.
I've been working in this
organisation for so many years now.
I've seen many Sonias
becoming Pari.
And then Pari becoming Kaya.
I've seen many girls getting ruined.
They are as dangerous
as they are benevolent.
You have challenged them.
You have called them for a fight.
I always mind my business, but...
I can't bear to see you
in this state.
You are different than others, Pari.
So you know what? Screw it.
You don't deserve to die.
You don't.
I can't do much for you,
but I can help you get away.
There's a two-mile long tunnel
beneath the house.
Use it.
Run away, Pari.
I don't know how you'll face
Mr Black and Kaya after you get out.
But for your pain,
I have these painkillers.
Your body can't take all that pain
without these pain killers.
My advice.
Take the painkillers, Pari.
Hi, Pari. Anything you want?
I've got instructions
not to let you out of this room.
I need some water
for the medicines.
Perhaps you could help me.
Sure.
What's going on?
It's Pari.
She's making a run for it.
Shut all the exits down.
- Yes, ma'am.
Pari is trying to make a dash?
- Yes.
What the hell is going on?
That f****ing woman!
Kaya, you made a mistake.
You should've killed me
along with Kabir.
Because I want to kill you
as long as I am alive.
You're making a mistake here.
Long shadows can
fool you into believing
that you're larger than life.
But you forget that long shadows
are created by the setting sun.
The only difference:
I know the sun has set for me.
I'm not afraid of the dark anymore.
I realised
why I couldn't save Kabir.
Because I never got
the training to save anyone.
But I know how to kill.
This gun wasn't loaded.
Think about it.
An unloaded gun made you feel
you were about to die.
Just imagine how you'll feel
when I have a loaded gun.
Pari has grown wings.
Now I'll soar in the sky.
Then I'll rain all that thunder
on you from above.
'Life can be so strange.'
'I was confined
when my beloved was alive.'
'Now that I am free,
my beloved is no more.'
'Now I had only one goal.'
'Revenge.'
'I wanted revenge.'
'I wanted to use their training
against them.'
'Kaya, Mr Black and
their secret organisation.'
'I wanted to destroy all of them.'
'All of them.'
Here's some wine for you, ma'am.
It's vintage white,
you'll like it.
Oh wow!
Thank you so much.
This is very kind. Thank you for it.
Such hard work.
Will you excuse me for a second?
And you are...
- Leena Singh.
I'm a very big fan of yours.
My fan!
News anchors don't have fans.
Well, they do.
Girls like me watch TV
for anchors like you.
Are you Indian?
- Yes.
I'm glad you support this charity.
I have to do charity
for this cause.
But I want to do
some charity for you.
For your career.
I didn't get you.
I have a major scoop every
journalist wants to have.
Meet in room 503 of this hotel.
I don't have much time.
Don't play this charity
drama over there.
I know you don't give a damn
about anything except your career.
I don't believe this.
Is this all true?
This is sensational.
I told you.
I'm a journalist.
So I know scoops like these
don't just fall into your lap.
What's in it for you?
Where is your phone?
- I have it. Why?
Start recording.
I'm ready to give
an on-camera confession.
What do you mean?
- I can prove whatever I am saying.
So come on now.
My name is Pari.
I used to work for
a shadow organisation
who was into stealing
and selling secrets.
I've shared all
the information with Mike Khan
which can used for exposing
this shadowy organisation.
Is it okay now?
Very good.
- Good.
Now it's your turn.
-My turn.
Even you can betray me
by selling this scoop.
I also need a guarantee.
What am I going to
confess on camera?
If you betray me,
then this sex tape will
reach your wife.
Even if it doesn't
destroy your career,
your marriage will fall apart.
My sex tape?
What are you saying?
I don't have a sex tape.
You'll have one now.
"I'm alive in your eyes."
"I'm the complaint on your lips."
"I'm in your life."
"I'll be there when I'm gone."
"Whether you see me or not,"
"I'm always with you."
"Hide me in your heartbeat."
"I'm your feeling."
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
'So as you've seen that
we have it from a strong source'
'that Aeronautics Avionics,'
'an English company
have sold missiles to Abu Hamza'
'at half the prize to beat
its Russian competitors.'
'that what they sold it
to the English government.'
'How can the English taxpayers
and government stand for this?'
'We're already trying to get
at the bottom of this.'
'The people whoever involved
will definitely be'
Tell them I'm not available.
- for such betrayal.'
'The British Government take it
very seriously.' - Kaya.
Abu Hamza is on his way here.
He is demanding a meeting.
Now I strongly recommend
that you meet with him.
You can't possibly
turn down everyone.
I can and I will.
I'm not meeting anybody today.
Do your job well
and make them go away.
Why the hell are you
not answering your phone?
It's my bloody choice.
I'll do as I please and
no one can stop me from doing so.
Try and explain
that to Mr Black.
He wants to see you now.
That was a brilliant move, Pari.
Very nice.
You pushed Kaya on the back foot
in one go.
Now she must answer
the Parliament and media.
You should be proud of yourself.
Doctor, the medicine
that you gave me,
gives me frequent hallucinations.
I mean...
I feel as if...
I see Kabir all the time.
I am really sorry.
I had no other quick way to
control your pain.
I had to give you
these strong painkillers.
It has opium in it.
So hallucinations
comes as a side effect.
To prevent one pain,
I must bear another pain.
To keep myself alive,
I must see Kabir dying
every now and then.
I warned you not to spoil her.
Did you see what happened?
Had you killed her before,
it wouldn't have come to this.
A moll has brought an organisation
to its knees.
During testing times, weak often
hurl accusations at each other.
We'll face challenges while
running such a big organisation.
I can deal with these challenges.
But then I think,
what's your use?
Many girls are recruited for you,
but you kill them
after a while.
This also causes a great loss
to our organisation.
You know it takes a huge investment
to turn a girl into an agent.
I get the feeling
that you can't handle
this responsibility anymore.
Mr Black,
Ms Pari is here to see you.
Rutherford, please take Kaya
to the next room
and make sure she stays there
till I finish my meeting with Pari.
I am impressed.
I hate backstabbers, but...
I like you.
You have been charming
even when you're an enemy.
Give me Kaya
and I'll spare your organisation.
If that doesn't happen,
I'll do whatever it takes
to reach Kaya.
I've already leaked a few secrets
to show my intent.
Before I do anything which sends
your organisation into disarray,
give me Kaya.
Oh!
You had just impressed me.
But now you do this.
Very bad, Pari.
People who issue threats
can't do anything.
Clouds that rain,
don't bring thunder.
I didn't come here
to threaten you, Mr Black.
I am here to offer you a deal.
Liabilities aren't good
for your business.
Right now, Kaya is a liability
for you.
You have two days.
offer valid till I change my mind.
Did you hear that?
You have two days
to become an asset
from a liability.
Or else
I'll accept Pari's offer.
Please tell me you found out
where Pari is hiding.
Yes, ma'am. She's at
the Tower Bridge room 504.
Well done, Kristov.
Now go get her.
I'll be waiting outside the hotel.
I need to see her body
hanging outside the hotel
for the whole world to see.
No problem, ma'am.
It should be fun.
I remember one of your tricks
so well.
Didn't you teach me,
it's not about the dog in the fight,
but the fight in the dog.
I've shot you with
a paralysing agent.
So no point trying to move.
You should've trusted your training
if not me.
Did you assume you'd
kill me so easily?
If I had my way,
you would've never found me.
But I wanted you to find me.
Would you like to see magic?
Look up.
Look at the poor guy
hanging between life and death.
If I call the hotel security
and say there's someone in my room,
they will rush in to help me.
Oh sorry, magic.
Yes.
Three.
Two.
One.
Did you like it?
You waited for my death,
but it was Kristov who died.
And now...
you are next.
Now you'll say I'm not for real.
Right?
You know all my inner thoughts.
Because you're akin to a thought
which lives in my mind.
I know you are not here.
I just can't convince myself.
Why do you fight yourself?
Why don't you accept
what you are feeling?
I saw you dying.
Feel me, Sonia.
If you can see me,
if you can hear me,
and if you can feel my touch,
then what prevents me
from being real?
"I'm right here, I just need a
bit of your faith to make me real."
"I just need a bit of place from you
so that I can descend down."
"I am a smoke, living on mercy."
"Turn me into your reality."
"I'm darkness, touch me
with your eyes, lend me your light."
"I'm always silent"
"But I am your voice."
"I know how to die,"
"but I also know how to live."
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
Kabir, I can't handle this!
'Every day I see you alive
and then I find you dead.'
'These medicines won't
keep me alive, they'll kill me.'
'Misfortune refuses to end for
the Khannas from Southall.'
'One of the sisters was jailed
for a murder and drug running'
'and now this shocking incident.
See the report.'
'I was very scared.'
'A few men drove here
at midnight'
'and they beat the hell out of her.'
'They said she had 24 hours,'
'or else she'd disappear
like her sister.'
'They left soon after
saying this.'
'The victim is Preet Khanna.'
'She is Sonia Khanna's sister
who died in prison.'
'Right now, Preet Khanna is fighting
for her life in City Hospital.'
'The police believe that a big
organisation is behind this attack.'
Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Have you seen this girl?
- Not really.
It's likely she'll be here.
If you spot this girl,
call me on this number.
Make sure.
- Sure.
Who are they?
What harm did my daughter
do to them?
I also don't understand that, aunt.
But they were asking about Sonia.
Maybe they were looking for Sonia.
It was Preet who suffered.
Doctor! Doctor!
Preet! Preet!
- Please, please.
Please step out.
Injection, please.
One, two, three.
Two, three.
Time of death: 1:55 pm.
We tried our best,
but we couldn't save your daughter.
I am so sorry.
I just don't understand
why we are being punished.
There can't be anyone
more unfortunate than us.
One daughter left us before.
And now we lost another.
Excuse me.
- Yes, madam?
I need this pill.
Okay, madam. Just wait here.
'Kaya made it clear
that no one was safe in this war.'
'First Kabir
and now my sister.'
'The next victim
could've been anyone.'
'Mom, Dad. Anyone.'
'I had only one chance.'
'I had only last move left.'
'A move that would'
'neutralise all my enemies.'
Soaib. - You and your force
are looking for me.
My name is Sonia Khanna.
AKA Pari.
Meet me if you want to
crack this big case.
What do you want in return?
Thank you.
So madam, you knew
I'd make you pay for this.
I could've arrested you
if I wanted to.
If you wanted to, you
would've brought the police force.
You know your brother is
a part of this racket.
If I am caught,
he'd be exposed.
There can be two reasons why
you're doing a solo investigation.
Either you are corrupt
or helpless.
Smart, very smart.
If you are not helpless
and want something in return
for the package you gave me,
then you must expose this racket.
Tonight, you must reach
the tunnel via the canal.
Tunnel?
Canal?
- I'll tell you about the palace
you've been looking for a while.
As for me, thank you for these
photographs and address.
Hello.
Sorry, Soaib.
I hate doing this.
Foot soldiers are often sacrificed
in major wars.
Hello. Is that Metropolitan Police?
I have a murder to report
in a town house outside London.
Kaya!
I knew Pari would come crawling
to me to save her last sister.
Right? - We have a problem,
you have to come with me.
Look.
What the hell?
She did it.
That bloody b**ch!
Pari has done this.
She exposed our racket
just like that. - What?
How? - She knew he was
Inspector Javed's brother.
So she killed him here.
I'm sure, she informed the police
after killing him.
The police will barge in here
any minute looking for him.
We can hide this dead body
somewhere else.
It's too late.
It's too bloody late.
Damn it!
S**t has hit the roof.
Kaya, you shouldn't have done it.
You shouldn't have
killed my brother.
Get out of
this bloody car, Kaya!
Get out now! Kaya!
Sorry, sir. It's a crime scene,
you can't go through.
We have information
that a cop is missing.
I'm going to leak
this story anyway.
You can keep me in or out.
We have the press over here.
'A policeman's dead body
has been found in a barn'
'in the outskirts
of London this morning.'
'The barn has a tunnel'
'that leads to a facility
where the girls are being trained'
'in secret to become
espionage agent.'
'Ms Kaya is here
to see Mr Black, sir.'
Tell her Mr Black
isn't seeing anyone.
He has other problems
to take care of.
That b***h has screwed us all.
I need to speak
to Mr Black right now.
She has turned the police against us
by killing Javed's brother.
Javed is out for revenge.
The media is creating a circus.
We are f***ked!
I have no idea
what you are talking about.
I think you should leave.
What?
You don't know who I am.
You f**king b****d.
If I go down,
I'm going to take you down with me.
I'm gonna have to call the police
if you don't leave
immediately, Miss.
When you get angry,
you can't think straight.
What do you mean?
Did you ever think
why Mr Black spared Pari
despite she made a huge mistake?
Because Mr Black is using Pari
against you.
Pari is Mr Black's weapon.
He can't do anything
and always remains in shadows.
So he is using your enemy
against you.
If you want to get Mr Black,
you have to get rid of Pari.
Maybe Mr Black sent you
to confuse me,
so that I'd target Pari
instead of him.
It's possible,
but it's not the case.
Like I just told you.
You aren't thinking this through.
Why are you helping me?
You may assume
that I must kill Mr Black.
If Pari has to die for this
then so be it.
I see.
I'm glad you do.
Now if you want
I can tell you
where Pari is right now.
I wish you wouldn't have
brought me at this juncture.
I made you Pari,
I gave you a new life.
Now I must take your life.
That's what you don't
understand, Kaya.
You didn't offer Pari any life.
Pari was born after someone died.
You can't kill someone twice.
Kids grow strong, but they can
never match their Mom.
Today, I've realised
that there's something
called karma.
You suffocated so many lives,
but today, you're suffocating.
Now just see how it feels
to be confined.
How it feels not to be
able to breathe?
You want to scream, but you can't.
How does it feel?
Feel it!
You try to run away from death,
but death lurks behind you.
See how that feels.
Feel it, Kaya.
What have you done, Pari?
How did she find out
you are here?
There are many
who could tell her the address.
You can say
that I wanted to let her know
my address.
Some are ambush predators
and some attack openly.
You want to take Kaya's place?
I don't want to
take anyone's place.
I want to move them
from their place.
Now it's the turn of
our common enemy.
Mr Black.
Pari.
It's not easy to kill Mr Black.
Forget killing him,
it's not easy to reach him.
I've made it till here, Doctor.
Now either my luck will help me
as it always has
or I'll die and go to Kabir.
I can't believe this.
Are you sure Kaya is dead?
Yes.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Pari is more dangerous than
we thought she is.
And now she is coming for Mr Black.
You must protect him
at any cost.
The doctor has informed me
that Pari has gone rogue.
She has killed Kaya
and now she's after Mr Black.
You need to keep Mr Black safe.
We'll make sure Mr Black
is protected at any cost.
Man all the doors,
keep an eye on all the CCTVs.
Check in every few minutes
on the radio.
Do you everything necessary.
Oh my God!
I told you,
Kaya didn't kill your brother.
Look at this.
What proof do you want?
How could a girl do it on her own?
Pari works alone
but she is the most dangerous.
She alone can match hundred killers.
You can catch her
if you listen to me.
What do you mean?
After killing Kaya, she'll
try to kill Mr Black.
She'll be where Mr Black is.
Mr Rutherford.
Won't you take me
to Mr Black now?
Everyone said
no one has seen Mr Black.
No one knows him.
But I had recognised you long ago.
I also found out about your ploy.
You made only one mistake.
'Clouds that rain,
don't bring thunder.'
You used the wrong phrase both
the times.
You should've said, clouds that
bring thunder don't rain.
But you said, clouds that rain,
don't bring thunder.
Two different people
can't make the same mistake.
So I understood
that you were using me
for getting rid of Kaya .
Kaya knew all your secrets.
She became a danger for you.
You sent photos to Kaya.
Because you knew she'd kill Kabir
and then I'd kill her.
Pari, to see you here now
makes me so proud of myself.
I knew I was right.
I knew you'd be the best.
And you are the best.
Then you must knew
I'd reach you.
The way you killed Kabir,
I'd also kill you.
So are you ready to die, doctor?
I've been ready for years.
But there is a twist in the tale.
You see.
Right on time.
Look behind you.
The police are here.
If you kill me,
you won't be able to save yourself.
I'm also ready to die.
I don't want to kill you.
You'll be sent to jail.
I know you aren't afraid of death.
But I also know
you are afraid to be confined
inside the four walls.
You aren't afraid of death,
but you're afraid of
a living hell.
Now you have two choices.
Either, take the exit
through this door.
Or else.
kill me and go to jail.
The choice is yours.
Come on.
Come on. Come on, Pari.
The police are on their way, hurry.
Come on, Pari. Don't think.
Will you run away or get caught?
Rutherford.
I think you should open the door
and let the police come in.
Nice move, Rutherford.
Not a nice move,
but a helpless move.
Hello.
Do you want to go back to jail?
Or do you want to be
the new Mr Black?
So.
Checkmate.
Open the door.
Quickly now.
- Open it!
We don't have much time.
Quickly!
Freeze! Don't move!
This is the man
who killed everyone.
Kaya.
Your brother Soaib.
If it wasn't for this brave,
young woman,
I'll be dead too.
Mr Rutherford.
Or should I say the new Mr Black?
The deal between you and me
was that I help you become Mr Black
and you never get in
touch with me.
Or see me ever again.
I know that, Pari.
I remember.
But there is something for
which I had to see you.
Only you can do this.
What is it?
- This
is Fidel Lanzov.
A Spanish millionaire.
I don't care who this is.
I am out of this game.
I know that, Pari. But please.
Listen.
It's not what you think.
You thought you could get out
that you could go away.
But they won't leave you.
In pictures, you see
Fatima al-Riyadhi.
She is an Arab girl.
They too fell in love
like us.
They dreamed of living together.
And then they were separated
like us.
In her country, girls
aren't allowed to fall in love.
Bring her back.
Fidel knows
only you can bring his
Fatima back.
The best in the business.
Please, Pari.
You can do this.
Only you can do this.
This isn't for money.
This is for love.
'That day I realised the truth.'
'I escaped one prison
only to enter another.'
'As long as we are alive,'
'we'll always be confined.'
'As long as
our soul is inside our body,'
'we'll be prisoners.'
'Only death can free us.'
'Since we have to live in prison,'
'I'd choose prison of love
over hate.'
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
"When a gentle breeze caresses you,"
"you'll feel my touch."
"When you see your face
in the mirror,"
"you'll find my reflection
in your face."
"At dawn, I flow through your tears
as morning."
"I was with you, I still am"
"I am not away from you."
"This life might change"
"I'm in every shade of it."
"Like an unseen shadow,"
"I follow you in the sun."
"I'll go wherever you go."
"I'll drown in you
and then I'll float again."
"I'm your love,
how can I ever die?"
"Oh my secret keeper!"
www.moviesubtitles.org