My dear people,
everyone is bound to feel that
our world is in a shocking mess.
It may not be worse than in other times,
but it seems so to us.
And after all, our world is like us.
We're not lacking plans to make
a more decent and peaceful world,
it's just that we don't have enough
good people to make our good plans work.
We must never relax for a single moment
in our work for a better world!
But the biggest and most helpful contribution
toward this that any of us can make...
is for us to become...
better people.
We must have more people
whose lives are motivated
by the kind of charity that St. Paul
wrote about long ago.
The kind that suffers long,
the kind that thinks no evil,
that kind that betters all things,
and endures all things.
St. Paul said the charity tops
the list of all virtues.
Buddha, Muhammad, Confucius,
Moses and the Nazarene agree...
that the golden rule of doing for others
as we would have them do unto us
is fundamental in bringing peace
and happiness to individuals,
and to our society.
All good people
have found gold in the golden rule.
Amen!
Mom, that lady is asleep.
Boo!
One more time, and I'll take you out
and spank you. You look up there. Go ahead!
Behave yourself.
Mr. Clayton,
one of the ushers took sick.
Would you mind serving in his place?
- Not at all.
Where are you going?
They want me to help with the collection.
But you'll look silly.
You're too tall to take up collection.
Besides, you're so clumsy!
What's- Where's Daddy going?
He's going to help take up collection, dear.
Where's Daddy?
He went to take up collection.
Oh, I think that's something
to laugh at.
That was Daddy.
- I know, dear.
- Naturally, who else?
Good morning, Mr. Clayton.
Hi, neighbors, going up in the snow?
Nice day for it. Where are you going?
No place. The car's broken down.
Oh that's too bad!
I'm sorry, Mrs. Butler.
And the children had their heart
set on it.
And I don't get another day off in weeks.
Now I don't know what to do with
all this food.
Why don't you folks take it and go
some place and enjoy yourselves?
No, thank you.
Oh, you're welcome, Mrs. Clayton.
I've got the answer. It's very simple.
Take our car.
- Thank you, Mrs. Clayton!
- Oh, sure.
Thanks, Mr. Clayton, thanks!
Isn't it great? They're tickled to death.
Oh, Mr. Clayton.
Would you call Nelson's garage?
It's in the book. Tell them
to come over and fix it.
I'll need it in the morning for work.
- Nelson's garage?
- Yes.
Sure. There.
Oh, would you wipe the windshield, please?
Sure.
Oh, that's good! I can see fine now.
Have you got everything in the car?
I forgot to feed the dog.
Oh, no!
Would you mind fixing him
a little dinner?
- No.
- Have you any lean meat?
Prince has such a weak stomach.
Well, the markets are closed today,
but we're having sweet bread.
Very easy to digest.
- Pan-broiled?
- Aha.
And maybe a little cottage cheese?
- Sure.
- Oh, that'll be fine.
Thank you, neighbors.
That's very generous of you.
There should be more
people like you Claytons.
You know... there should be less people
like the Butlers.
Incidentally, does it bother you that you
loaned the car to a man who can't see?
Well, I never thought of that.
But he's got good thick glasses.
Well, maybe he's driving with
his reading glasses.
- Morning, Lulu.
- Morning, Daddy.
- Morning, Butch.
- Hiya, Pop.
Hat off...
Please pass the Krispys.
Krispy Krunchies again, huh?
You've been eating those for two weeks.
Only eleven more packages and
I'll get my Indian suit.
Oh... and what's it that Lulu gets?
She gets to see me in my Indian suit.
And then you said you'd help me get...
a doll.
Sure, after I get my football.
He gets always the best of it, Daddy.
I eat everything, and he gets everything.
You shouldn't talk with your mouth full.
Say, Pop, isn't there something you can eat
that can win mom a new house?
Alright. You find out what it is,
and I'll eat it.
What's so funny?
- Your son just pulled a nifty.
- Oh, what was it?
Oh, just something between us men.
Hey!
Where's Chloe?
She must have missed the bus.
Monday's her bad morning anyway.
Mm, it's a break for me.
I like this cook better anyway.
Scrambled eggs and...
Canadian bacon...
fries and scallop...
Oh, you're so talented.
You don't say it!
Please, Mr. Clayton,
my brother will be down any minute.
No, he won't. I called him, and he just...
rolled over and played dead.
Oh, did he?...
- Do you suppose he'd mind if we ate?
- Beg your pardon?
Mommy, what are you and Daddy doing?
Nothing!
I'll be with you in a minute.
Here comes old sleepy-head.
Clever kid.
Morning, Claude.
Morning.
Didn't you sleep?
No. Bad night.
Ready? Here's our breakfast.
Well, here's yours...
and, uh... here's yours.
What did you do in the Navy,
have breakfast in bed?
Yeah...
The Admiral used to bring me a tray.
Claude, if it isn't asking too much,
you are a guest in the house.
Not for long!
Oh, I've realized six months
isn't a long time,
but while you are here the least you could do
is cooperate, and eat when we eat.
Couldn't you have gotten up earlier
this morning?
What for? The labor office
doesn't open till ten.
Yeah, the government won't send
the cheque to the house,
he has to go all the way downtown
and stand in line.
No! Does the government know this?
I'll have to write my senator about it.
Well, a fine way to talk
about your own brother.
Oh, forgive me, Claude,
I didn't know what I was saying.
I've been standing over hot stove
all morning.
Home on the range!
Uncle Claude?
Are you an idiot?
Somebody's been talking...
Now, you kids better get ready
for school now.
Yes. Both of you, rush it.
Come on, scoot!
All right, get up!
Neither one of you will laugh when I'm rich!
Oh, the heck we won't!
Lu, are you going to the funeral?
Whose funeral?
Oh, Lu. Poor Harry Gilmore.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear it.
But I hardly knew Henry Gilmore.
Harry.
Was he the man who borrowed
the 180 dollars from the bank
and you guaranteed payment?
Yep, poor Harry.
Did he leave the widow any...?
No. Sick a long time.
Very sad.
I'm sure he was a wonderful man,
but don't you think at times
you have too much faith in people?
Lu, how can you have
too much faith in people?
I know it sounds terrible,
but people imposed on you.
You're a soft touch.
You always said you can picture you and me
by our own fireside.
Well, 180 dollars would build
a pretty nice fireplace,
in a home we're never going to get.
Look, Lu.
I don't regret it.
Harry Gilmore was a fine man.
He happened to need some money,
and I saw that he got it.
Of course.
Everybody thinks well of Harry Gilmore.
Say one thing wrong with Harry Gilmore.
His health!
Hey, she's got something there!
Say, can I have a cup of coffee
before you two go broke?
Say, who can that be?
Claude, would you mind if...?
Why... no! Go ahead.
Oh, the telephone. Claude...
I've got it.
Hello.
Yes, I'll accept the charges.
Hello?
Well, hello, Mr. Butler.
How are you?
And your wife and the children?
Uh-huh.
And... how is our car?
Well, that's good.
What?
Oh, you're staying another day.
Oh, it's alright, Mr. Butler.
Our children will get to school.
We'll manage somehow.
Oh, think nothing of it!
Sam will get to work.
That's alright.
What?
Feed the dog? Again?
Uh-huh. And no canned food.
Oh yes, I'll balance his
diet carefully.
Well, have a good time!
By all means.
Lou, this is Mr. Nelson, the garage man.
Hello, Mr. Nelson!
He's gonna have a cup of coffee with us.
He is?
Oh, well, Mr. Nelson, sit right here.
Take this.
Oh, here...
Oh, and... the Krunchies too, please.
Thank you.
Sam, what's Mr. Nelson doing here?
Oh, he fixed the Butlers' car.
- The brushes on the carburetor were fluctuating.
- You don't say!
The Butlers' bill.
Coffee?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Oh, yeah.
There you are.
You see, Mrs. Clayton, I run
my business on a cash basis.
With me, cash is king,
why, if I trusted people
I'd starve to death.
You'd be surprised how many people
don't pay.
Oh no, I wouldn't.
Oh, if you could measure
the number of deadbeats
there are in this world,
absolutely worthless, no good-
Have you met my brother Claude?
- Glad to know you.
- Charmed.
- Don't you think there's a lot in what I said?
- No, not much.
Firstly, I think there's two sides
to everything,
including my face,
which I'm now going to shave.
Oh, he's only my half-brother.
Well, that's nice.
As I was telling Mr. Clayton,
he's the one who called for my services,
and he's the one who should pay.
But it isn't our car,
why should he have to pay the bill?
Well, the Butlers have been
our neighbors for a long while.
You can trust them.
They'll pay you, all right?
If you can trust them so much, you pay me,
and they can pay you, or I'll take the car back.
Oh... Well, then I- I'll give you the money.
5, 10, 15...
Oh, Sam, I forgot
to tell you.
The Butlers phoned and said
they're not bringing the car back.
They decided to stay another day.
The weather's so beautiful.
16, 17...
They did, huh?
18, 50, 75. Got any money, Lu?
Well, no, I haven't.
I was expecting some of that.
Would you like to use
the children's lunch money?
Oh, Lu.
That's near enough.
He said that was near enough.
Well, we're really in a fine fix now.
The kids will have to walk to school,
and I'll have to go with them.
- It's only six blocks.
- And six back.
And how are you going to get to work?
Unless you use the Butlers' car,
say, how about that?
Well, I wouldn't think of using their car
without asking them.
No, you wouldn't...
Well, I-
Sir, you brew a mighty fine bean.
Great coffee, sign of a great cook.
She certainly is.
She cooked me a wonderful breakfast.
Sure smells good.
Especially on an empty stomach.
- Haven't you eaten yet?
- No...
Lu.
I've got it.
Mr. Nelson, how would you like your eggs,
the same way?
Well, now that you ask,
thank you, ma'am, no.
Have you ever fixed them
with black butter?
- No.
- Well, you burn a little butter in the saucepan,
and you put the vinegar and the eggs
in a little casserole,
and then you ta-... Of course there's always
eggs Florentine if you have fresh spinach.
No, but we could plant some.
No, that won't be necessary.
Eggs and black butter's quite a dish.
I'll bet if you tried it once,
your husband will want it all the time.
Incidentally, that's very funny,
what she said about planting the spinach.
Your wife's got quite a sense of humor.
Yeah. Has yours?
No, she's got asthma.
It's awful.
She's no fun at all.
I bet you have a picnic with her!
Oh, yeah, she's a barrel of fun.
I'll fix your eggs, Mr. Nelson.
You certainly did alright for yourself.
Now, you take my wife...
I don't know, she's...
she's got a kind of a horse face.
Oh, Mr. Nelson, I've seen some
mighty pretty horses.
- I had a beautiful big horse.
- My wife's big too.
His name was Baldy.
Say, that's funny. She's getting a little
bald spot too, right on top.
I'm gonna start calling her Baldy.
No...
No, I guess I better not. I gotta watch
I don't get too funny, on account of her asthma.
It gets her to laughing,
and it gets her to wheezing.
Sometimes she sounds like a whistle.
Sometimes she sounds like a foghorn.
My wife's grandmother had the same trouble.
She looked like a horse, huh?
No, just... just asthma.
- Morning, miss Lou.
- Hello, Chloe.
I just missed the bus.
Waiting for the streetcar.
Oh, that man of mine!
This no-good little casino.
Did you have trouble
getting him up this morning?
Gettin' 'im up? No, he didn't come
home at all, that little fool.
He thinks he has found a new
Linda Horn.
All she is is lean...
What she's got I ain't got twice as much of?
I take over, Mrs. Lou.
Who are we feeding?
Brother Claude?
Well, look-
See here, who's that?
Mr. Sam asked him to move in too?
I'm quitting! Yes, sir, I cer-
He's just here for breakfast.
Miss Lu...
How does Mr. Sam find
to find all these characters?
I've tried to break him of it, Chloe,
but he just loves people.
Yes, miss...
My man loves people too,
but he loves them off the premises.
How does this one want his eggs?
On black butter.
No foolin'? Black butter?
Black butter! I got to take
another look at that...
- Morning, Mr. Clayton!
- Morning, Chloe.
- Morning.
- Morning... Good morning.
And don't forget, take his eggs off
in exactly 33 seconds.
Lu, his wife has asthma, bad.
She has? Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah... she's a mess!
You oughta see what I go through...
His wife has asthma.
Is it contagious?
Hey, Lu, what are we gonna do
about his poor wife's asthma?
Well, I don't know, Sam,
but I'll work on it.
I'll write to Johns Hopkins
and buy a medical journal.
No, no, Lu...
I mean that goose grease remedy
of your grandmother.
It helped Buch's croup a lot.
Couldn't you make a little batch of it
for Mrs. Nelson?
Sam...
That takes four hours.
It's Monday.
Chloe and I have-
I can come back later.
No bother.
I got a hunch it will help her a lot.
She can't go through life
sounding like a foghorn.
Oh, it'd be a blessing if you
could cure her...
All right, all right.
I'm sold.
Come on, kids. It's almost nine.
Mother'll take you.
Sam, you better get going too.
Well, I always say one good turn
deserves another,
I'd like to drop your children off at school,
and take you on to work.
Thank you. Did you hear that, Lu?
Mr. Nelson is gonna drop us off in his car.
Oh, that's very nice of you,
Mr. Nelson.
Yeah, bread up on the water, as I always say.
I'll be back for the goose grease.
Goodbye, little mother.
- Around lunchtime?
- A little later, about three.
Oh, no!
Chloe, Chloe! Come here,
you gotta see this.
There you go.
They're so cute.
- Bye!
Be careful!
Imagine, the general manager
of our leading department store!
He doesn't care.
- Good morning.
- Good morning. Good morning. How are you?
- Well, Mrs. Kelly, hello.
- Hello.
Say, how is that little baby of yours?
- Oh, he's just fine.
- Wonderful.
Remember her?
- Finnerty?
- Yes.
Of course, we've met
at your baby's christening.
Say, and how many teeth does he have now?
He has five.
Three upper, two lower.
Five teeth altogether?
Three upper and two lower?
Yes.
Hey, her ba-
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Mr. H.C. Borden, our president.
Mrs. Kelly and Mrs. Finnerty.
Oh, how do you do, I'm delighted.
How do you do, Mr. Borden.
Her baby has five teeth already,
and he's not more than... What? Eight?
- Eight months old.
And her boy will be graduating
from military academy in...
June?
Why, that's right, Mr. Clayton!
Isn't that wonderful?
Such a memory!
And he's a great big fellow too.
Why, he's that much taller than you are.
Well, well...
Uh, what can I do for you?
- Well, uh...
- I'd like to see something in teething range.
Teething range?
- Oh, yes... For the little fellow?
- Yes.
Of course.
Upstairs please, the third floor,
and the first counter on the right
as you come out of the elevator.
Sam!
- ... to miss Harrington.
- Thank you!
- All right!
Why didn't you escort them up
personally?
It's not every day we sell
a teething ring. No.
Now, Sam, this is our biggest season, so...
don't waste time getting people's names
and how many teeth the baby has.
Well, we wait all year for Christmas!
You can have the other eleven months,
but give me that Yuletide season.
You know, Sam, when sentiment runs high,
that's the time to make the kill.
So keep your eyes peeled for confused
fathers and husbands.
They'll buy anything.
And it's our job to see that they get it.
- Excuse me.
- This is the ti-
Can you tell me where
Humboldt Street is?
822 1/2 Humboldt Street.
This is near Claremont.
There's a city directory over there
by the phone booth, madam.
You know Sam, we can't milk Easter very much.
Father's Day's all right, moving neckties,
but for Christmas, ha, ha!
I'll have you know I broke my glasses,
and it wouldn't do me any good
to look it up in your old directory.
Can I be of any help?
Yes, I can see that your mother
taught you manners.
I'm an orphan myself.
Are you acquainted with our city?
No, I just came in on the train.
That's how I broke my glasses.
I was in the dining
car, and we hit a curve...
There they went! They smashed...
Well, that's too bad. Well, that's about
eleven blocks from here,
Let's see. This is Main, go down Main
five blocks to Elm,
one short block to the right
will bring you to Sycamore...
Oh, dear... That's too many streets.
Or maybe this will help you.
Here we are,
right here, five blocks down Main... Elm...
- Yes...
Now be careful at this intersection,
it's very dangerous.
- Five blocks...
- Yes, let me look at that...
...to Humboldt.
- Now, right about here is 822.
- And I'll find the house!
I bet you will.
That's very nice of you.
If I can't get this, really, I-
I oughta have my head examined, hadn't I?
Good bye.
Sam, I want to talk to you.
Up to now, you've solved the teething lady,
you've drawn a map showing people
how to get to Humboldt Street.
Personally, I'd rather hear
the cash register ring.
Well, maybe they'll be back some day
and make your cash register ring.
Sam, you and I don't see
eye to eye on anything.
You told all the department heads they can take
two hours off to go to Harry Gilmore's funeral.
It's bad enough that I have to go.
He was your advertising manager
for thirty years.
I paid him for thirty years.
If they want to make a big thing out of it,
why don't they bury him at night?
Then everybody could go on their own time.
Hey, how about that?
People are born at night, people die at
night ...
They even play night baseball,
don't they?
But you just don't bury people at night.
- Well, they shouldn't bury them on my time, then...
- I beg your pardon.
May I have a free sample
of your new cold cream
that you're advertising and demonstrating?
There's your man. He'll direct you.
- We'll take the elevator.
- Thank you.
Here I am again.
What's the matter, did you lose the map?
No, I was just walking along,
and I got to thinking...
Hello there.
I was just telling one of your clerks here
that I was walking along...
This is Mr. H.C. Borden,
our president.
- How do you do?
- President? He?
Not...?
Oh! I thought you were president.
Well, anyway...
You were so sweet about
telling me all those directions,
I remembered something I needed.
And I thought... why not buy it
from that nice young man?
Well, I'm sure that whatever it is you want, we have.
What did you have in mind?
Have you any knitting needles?
What kind? Steel or bone?
And... what kind of yarn?
Oh, I wouldn't know.
You see, I'm just taking it up.
I have a granddaughter.
Don't tell me you're a grandmother!
Stop it, you fool!
She's going to be married.
She's going to marry the nicest young man,
and... I'm gonna be alone
a great deal from now on.
So I thought I'd take up knitting.
Well, what do you intend to knit, a sock,
or... perhaps a hug-me-tight, huh?
I had in mind, uh... a turtleneck sweater.
For a giraffe!
Well, seriously, what would you like to knit?
I thought I'd like to start on those
Argyle socks that everybody's knitting.
Well, Argyles are a little tricky
to begin with...
First, of course, you'll have to learn
how to knit and pearl.
That's the basis.
That's where you have to start.
- But... we give lessons.
- And they're free!
Couldn't she just use our needles until
she decides whether she likes it or not?
Oh, I'll buy them.
And speaking of buying...
I plan to buy Johnny and Rhoda
a wedding present in Chillicothe,
and ship it here to them.
But if I bought it here, it'd save
all that freight, wouldn't it?
Yes, it would.
I believe in giving things to people
when they're young, don't you?
So I'm furnishing their house complete.
With everything. Stove,
refrigerator, washing machine,
silverware, linen, just everything.
And- And I'll need your help, to remind me
in case I forget anything.
It'll cost several thousand dollars,
but they're young!
It'll certainly make Rhoda and Johnny
very happy.
You know, Johnny's name's Camel.
This is gonna be very funny.
When Rhoda marries him, she
will be Rhoda Camel (rode a camel)!
Camel? Get it?
He doesn't get it.
What's that?
Phi Beta Kappa?
You don't think it's funny?
You know, sometimes I wander...
- Where is the furniture department?
- Furniture?
Thank you so much!
Haven't got all day, you know,
I'm running on a schedule!
You might run it with a little courtesy too.
You know, if it hadn't been for you, mister,
he'd have waited until I got just in front of the bus, and...
then run over me.
Wouldn't have been a bad idea at that.
What's all the hurry these days?
Where's everybody going?
Absolutely no consideration
for anybody else.
That's why it's a pleasure
to meet a person like you.
I would've had to wait twenty minutes for another bus,
and I have a dentist appointment.
And you know how hard it is
to get them these days.
Oh, yes.
You know, none of us go
to the dentist often enough.
And don't let anyone ever tell you
to have your wisdom teeth out.
Because if I didn't have my wisdom teeth...
he wouldn't have had anything to bridge to!
See?
That's the one. And this!
You get what I mean?
I can't begin to thank you!
Thank goodness for people like you.
Most people are so...
thoughtless and rude these days.
I was telling my husband, only the other day...
I bet he gets cauliflower ears
from listening to her.
You're paid to run the bus,
not to insult the passengers.
It all started with Sir Galahad here
stopping the bus,
making a hero out of himself.
Don't lose your temper, mister.
It takes all kinds of people
to make a world.
From a distance, he must have
thought she was pretty.
For that, I'll have to report him.
What's your number?
Here's the whole description,
take it all down.
Just as I thought!
No hair!
I'm not surprised!
Nothing could grow on a head like that!
- Oh, you...
Here it is, all in his hat.
Melvin Z. Wurtzberger.
Melvin Z. Wurtzberger!
You know, it's really
people like you, mister...
- Yes, you've said that before.
- ... that restore...
Would you let me off at
the next corner, please?
Why, just stick around, Bob,
maybe she'll bake you a cake?
Why don't you shut that
big fresh face of yours?
Don't worry, this is his last day
with the railroad company.
I'm sorry!
What was I to think?
She was running there very fast.
I thought she wanted to get in the bus.
Well, look, don't get-
Melvin's same words...
- Morning, Ruthie.
- Morning, Mr. Clayton.
I like this department.
It's a wonderful number!
Shirley May is feeling better.
Worse.
She seems to be jumping...
Yes, she's jumping all right.
Her next jump will be off a bridge,
mark my words.
She's got those "when I woke up this morning,
he was gone" blues.
I was out with them half a dozen times.
And he even told me
he was going to marry her.
The yellow so-and-so...
Didn't have nerve enough
to tell it to her himself.
He wrote to the landlady, and she gave
Shirley May the news with her eviction notice.
- That's rough.
- Yeah...
I'd take her in myself, Mr. Clayton,
you know that,
but my husband, the kid and myself
are all in one room.
It's pretty crowded, you know,
you were at the wedding reception, remember?
If she doesn't get a break, you're going
to be reading about her in the newspapers.
Number one on the Hit Parade
in a month, I guarantee.
Shirley May, may I speak to you?
Ruth, will you take over from there?
Well... you've made a lot of sales already,
I'm gonna make a note
to get you a little raise.
Oh, but I'm quitting, Mr. Clayton.
- You're quitting?
- Yes.
Well you are... Sit down.
You know, your department has done
wonderfully since you took over.
Why quit?
Because I can't stand it anymore,
Mr. Clayton.
Singing those songs gets me down, I-
Now look...
You've got only one problem.
Where are you gonna sleep tonight?
Now, I'm gonna give you
the rest of the day off,
and you're going out and try
to find yourself a place to stay.
If you don't have any luck,
give me a call, and I'll try
to find you something.
You're too young and too... pretty and...
- Oh, sure.
You're attractive enough to get a single man!
Here.
Put on a new face.
Start a new life, hmm?
Nice people, the Claytons.
Oh, Mr. Nelson!
How are you?
And this is Mrs. Nelson,
I take it.
Yeah, this is her.
Well, we just came by to congratulate you.
That goose grease of yours
did the trick, Mrs. Clayton.
Helped her a lot.
I'm sure grateful to you, Mrs. Clayton.
Well, we just stopped by to return your jar.
I filled it with some of my special
meat sauce.
Oh, you shouldn't have done that!
It's very nice of you.
Well...
Thanks.
I hope we didn't come at the wrong time.
You're in dinner hour, I think, like that...
I'd, uh... I'd  like to invite you
to stay the dinner ...
Alright.
I mean, if we had, uh... But you
couldn't've picked a worse evening.
We just have a little sort of a... a...
it's nothing really.
Chloe says "come and get it".
That roast beef, that Yorkshire pudding
and then golden-brown potatoes are awaiting!
Lu?
- Oh, hello, Mr. Nelson.
- Glad to see you, Mr. Clayton.
- And this is...?
- Yeah.
This is the missus, the one
I was telling you about.
Well, hello.
Well, uh... thanks again.
That meat sauce of ours will go
wonderful on... your roast beef.
Well, uh... say, Claude won't be here tonight...
That's what I say, Sam.
Won't you come in?
Well, we can't stay long, but just...
Chloe!
Now, everybody just my meat sauce,
tell me how you like it.
Is that the same jar the goose grease was in?
Don't worry, little man.
I scoured it thoroughly with soap and water!
I quite agree. I can still taste the soap!
Butch!
It's very tasty.
What do you put in it, Mrs. Nelson?
Well, first...
I know. Soap!
Butch!
Come on, kids, let's go to the kitchen.
- Vegetables, or...?
- Oh, sorry.
They're gonna have their dinner
in here, Chloe.
I thought so...
Now, I want you two to finish your dinner
without a peep out of either one of you.
Chloe, let me know if they don't behave,
will you?
Yes sir.
Oh, Sam, Mr. Nelson is just saying
his wife sells real estate.
Well, do you think this would be
a good time to buy, Mrs. Nelson?
Well, mark my word, prices won't be
any lower in our time.
Would you be willing to trade this house in?
We don't own it.
You don't own your own home,
a man in your position?
Clayton...
If the price was right, what type of a home
would you be interested in?
Well, I've always had my heart set on
an early American farmhouse style.
Well, there is one...
It's not on the market yet.
The owner built it himself, he's an architect
and he may go to South America.
And she brought all her own furniture
from Connecticut.
Oh, no!
It sounds just like my dream home!
Look.
- This!
- Well, look at that...
Why, it's enough like it
to be the same house!
- Really?... Sam, did you hear that?
- Yeah.
When will you know?
When will he know?
Well, he's waiting to hear
from South America.
Oh Sam, wouldn't it be wonderful
if we could get it?
I mean, if they didn't ask too much, huh?
Yes, if the price is decent.
What's the matter?
Don't you want to buy a house?
Oh, excuse me, I'll answer that.
- Want some more meat sauce?
- Oh, no. Thank you.
Sister dear!
- Yes, brother dear.
- Please pass the soap.
- You have only the two?
- Yes.
Tell me, how many bedrooms
are there in the house?
Well, there's three bedrooms and a den
that can be used for a spare.
Oh, that's fine. We can use the extra room
because of the children.
Have you any?
I'm sorry, but this is very important.
Someone wants to see me,
that owes me some money.
They may pay me.
- Oh, no, Sam. Well, by all means, get your things!
- Well, I didn't want to leave you...
- With us?...
- No, I didn't mean...
- Shoot it clean, Sam!
Sam, I'll be perfectly alright.
Oh, our dearest friend!
Welcome to our domicile!
And here's little mother,
isn't she beautiful?
- Hello.
- Hello!
Oh Sam, we're just bursting with happiness,
thanks to you.
Sam, I won't kiss you, but I would like
to extend a right hand loaded with gratitude.
Come on, sit down.
We asked you over here because...
well, we didn't know yet whether you
told Lu anything about our loan.
No, it's better this way.
How's business?
Great, great! We got the busiest
little gas station in the county,
and things are getting better all the time.
I'm gonna build a little one-room
and bath in the rear of the station,
we're gonna live there too.
You see, that way we'd be...
saving the rent on this thing.
That is, if... you think that's a good idea.
I've got all the
materials ordered.
I can cancel it though, if
you don't think it's wise.
No, I- I think it's a good idea.
Oh, when do you think you'll be able
to start paying me back?
Well, the way business is going, I think
I can start paying you next month.
We should have it all paid off within six.
Sam, I hope you feel alright
about this thing, because...
well, sometimes we worry because...
you haven't told Lu.
Oh, no, I think it'll be better
to surprise her when you pay me.
Much better.
I'd have been home earlier,
only that... the darned car...
- What's the matter?
- Stalled three times.
It'll never be the same.
Did anybody pay you, or could you have
stayed here and have a nice dinner?
Well, it wasn't wasted time, but...
I'll explain to you later.
- Oh, they didn't pay you.
- No.
Well, did you have a barrel of fun
with the Nelsons?
Oh, sure.
When they finally left,
I took a hot bath for my nerves.
And then, what do you think happened?
Before you go any farther,
let me tell you I'm...
I'm sorry for wishing all these people on you.
It isn't fair. I'm through getting you
in all these things.
No more Nelson ruining our dinner,
no more Butlers ruining our car...
Speaking of Butler,
that four-eyed Ford flusher,
now it can be told: he put
a great big dent in our fender!
Which cost me $8.75 more!
- No!
- Yes.
I figured, why ask him for it, when the deadbeat
won't pay me the $19 he owes me now.
- And, I didn't want to tell you about it-
- Well, that's alright, Sam.
Well, I thought you might, um... rub it in.
Who, me?!
Oh, no!
No? You wouldn't?
- You're not mad at me?
- No.
Lu, you're a darling.
Let's forget about other people tonight.
Alright, if we can.
Sure we can.
Let's be selfish, and just, uh...
Just think about ourselves, huh?
And the heck with the Nelsons!
And the heck with the Butlers!
Oh, Sam, please!
What's the matter? Can't you concentrate
on your husband?
I'm doing my best.
Well, does my love border on the ridiculous?
Yes. In a way, yes.
You know me, don't you?
Sam? Your husband?
- But Sam, you don't understand.
- I... don't unders-
- You remember the Butlers, don't you?
- Butlers, huh?
Good evening.
- Hello.
I suppose you think I'm... quite a flirt.
So I hope I didn't shock you.
No. You don't always keep
your shades down, you know?
So what's so funny, what's the joke?
I suppose you're wondering why
we're here at this hour.
Yes, I certainly am.
Isn't it something we
can take up tomorrow?
No.
Well, you thought it was going
to cost you only $27, didn't you?
I mean, for the Butlers
to have a picnic with your car.
Well, you haven't heard the half of it.
They really had a picnic.
They turned the other car over.
The other car?
It was his fault!
That's right!
Mr. Butler was driving on,
minding his own business,
when suddenly, right in front of him...
But then it was too late, wasn't it,
Mr. Butler?
Yes, much.
Say, what's the idea?
You didn't tell me you had an accident
when you brought the car back.
Well, I didn't want to worry you.
I thought I could talk to the fellow,
and that he'd be reasonable, and...
I did have a nice talk with him
down in the ravine.
Good. Quiet, Lu.
But... when I heard what he wanted,
it was just ridiculous,
I knew you'd never pay that.
Me? What about you?
Well, that just what I told him,
I said "Look,"
"If you're going to sue anybody,
sue me."
"Don't sue a nice guy like Sam Clayton,"
"It wasn't his fault."
Except, uh...
Legally, it was your car!
He said he looked me up, and I have a
reputation for not paying my bills.
Just because I haven't been working!
I lost my job, incidentally.
See, you tried to do us a favour, and...
he lost his job because of you!
- Well...
- That's how life is.
- If you hadn't loaned us your car...
- Your car!
That's where it all started.
Now, I'll tell you how it happened.
This is fascinating. Oh, pardon me,
go ahead, Mr. Butler.
You don't have to. It will be in the complaint,
all written up, and I can read it.
Good night.
Don't you wanna go too?
Everything happens to us...
Just when we were trying so hard
to save some money too.
I know exactly how you feel.
We've been trying to save money
to buy a home,
haven't we, dear?
- We sure have.
It's the same with us. Some day
we hoped to get his eyes fixed.
Never mind about my eyes.
That's what they're going to say,
they're gonna try and give me that old eye test.
We'll fight this together!
I can see as well as the next fellow.
Oh, thanks.
Over there, dear.
- Oh...
- Over there.
Where will they put them next?!
What were you thinking of, dear?
Do you want to pick me up
and start all over again?
You're darned right I do.
Oh, oh, do you have a first-aid kit?
He hit his head on one of those
potted plants,
you shouldn't have those things
hanging there,
this is getting to be, oh...
I know you've heard this before,
but I'm sorry again...
Yes, I know, dear.
But now we have a lawsuit on our hands.
Our home is farther away than ever.
Damages, attorneys fees...
If this keeps up, we won't be able
to buy a tent!
We just can't go on like this.
Sam... When are you going to learn
that there's some people in this world
who don't deserve your help?
Just think of the people you've done things for
since we've been married.
Then think of how many have paid you back.
Take Claude, for instance...
he's sleeping in my bed, our bed...
with you!
Butch is in there on the cut,
and I'm here with Lulu.
For how long?...
Sam, we have no life of our own.
This isn't what my mother told me at all.
- Honey, we've tried every other arrangement...
- Except to throw my brother out.
Oh, I know- I know he was badly wounded,
and I tried to make allowances for it,
but, Sam, he's got to move!
- Oh, I think Claude's got a lot of...
- Lead?
I can't throw him out until he finds himself.
But he's not even looking for himself!
Oh, I know it's ungrateful to say that
about a man who's done so much
for his country,
but... if- if he'd just go away somewhere.
Maybe he could find himself in South Africa.
A lot of people find themselves there!
I know- I know how you feel.
I'm not too happy in there myself.
Us... we three boys.
Who could that be at this hour?
I'll find out.
Whoever it is there, be firm.
Not another nickel!
Not another nickel! Shhh...
And if they refuse the charges, hang up!
Your brother is not coming home tonight.
Can we depend on that?
Yes... He's going to Cincinnati.
No!
Yes, for ten days!
Goodie! Maybe he'll
find himself there.
- Yeah.
- What's he going to do?
There's a big music festival.
Everybody's coming from miles around.
Not my brother.
What's he going to do?
- Shoot pool.
- That's more like him.
There's a big tournament, he's pretty good,
you know.
So I hear. I think pool's very nice.
Don't you?
Yeah, pool's a very interesting game,
a very old game,
and I think it's very nice of Claude to call
and let us know, don't you think?
Daddy! Mommy!
Daddy, now you have to tell me a story!
Alright. Which story do you want?
Cinderella!
First we've got to get in the bed.
Now, we keep her up.
There!
Now, once upon a time there was
a little girl named Cinderella.
And... she had two wicked sisters.
And didn't she have a wicked aunt too?
Oh, yeah, she used to make Cinderella
work from morning until dark.
Well, anyway, along came
a fairy godmother,
and changed little Cinderella into a
beautiful princess.
What about the mice, Daddy?
What mice?
The fairy godmother had some mice.
Oh, she did? Oh, yeah.
And she, uh... And she turned the mice
into six beautiful white horses.
That's right!
So Cinderella went out to the garden and
brought a great big pumpkin, and...
and, uh... gave to the horses.
- No!
- No?
And she gave it to the... fairy godmother.
And the fairy skinned it, and turned it
into a six... I mean, a carriage.
That's right, I remember now!
And she hooked up the six white horses
to the pumpkin, I mean, the carriage,
and told Cinderella to jump in the carriage,
and... away they went. Hmm?
And they went away- They went to the ball.
Yeah. They went to the ball.
Now, Cinderella...
... was all- She was changed into a
beautiful princess by this time, wasn't she?
- Yeah.
- And... oh! Boy, what a princess!
Where was I? Oh, yeah.
Oh, well, uh...
Beautiful princess!
Oh, she was so beautiful, she...
Oh, gosh.
What a beautiful princess!
Oh, yeah, and she lost her shoe...
And she had so many children,
she didn't know what to do.
Oh, Daddy, that's another story!
And they were all hungry besides.
So she went to the cupboard,
and the cupboard was bare...
So the poor bear had none.
Well, anyway, where was I?
Let me tell you a story, Daddy,
and you go to sleep!
Alright.
So Cinderella waited and waited...
for days and days...
The question was, would she
and Prince Charming...
... ever... get together?
... when suddenly, the door opened,
and there he stood, the prince himself!
So everybody in the fairyland
went to sleep.
Three little pigs went to sleep,
the big bad wolf went to sleep...
Little Miss Muffet was so tired,
she collapsed and fell on a tuffet.
and the spider went to sleep beside her.
Everybody was so tired!
Even the Sandman had stopped counting
the sheep in the meadow...
the cows in the corn...
Everybody's asleep but us...
Just you and me.
What's the matter?
No!...
Boo!
Well... What happened?
I've got a surprise for you!
I've given up pool.
- He's given up-
- Yes, I heard.
You hung up so fast, I thought
you were disgusted with me!
Oh, no, it- what...
Say, what's the occasion?
What are you two all dolled up for?
Oh, this is just...
What was it?
We were just celebrating
the longest day of the year.
Yes, that is.
Oh... I don't get it!
Mommy!
You explain it to him.
I'll tell Lulu another story.
Forever, uh... Goldilocks.
I'll get it, Sam.
Is this Samuel R. Clayton's house?
- Yeah, uh-huh.
- I'm Sam Clayton.
Mm... yeah...
Look, I got a girl in the back of my car,
and she's in bad way.
She had me stop at the drugstore
for a minute,
I should got wise then,
but I didn't.
Next thing I know, I look in the mirror,
I don't see her.
I turns around and there she is,
out on the floor.
Uh... but look, this is a private residence.
Why don't you take her to a receiving hosp-
Yeah, I know...
Look, buddy, I wouldn't act so wise
if I was in your shoes, you know.
I might be doing you a favour!
I just didn't find the sleeping pills,
I found your card, Samuel R. Clayton!
Oh, I know who it is. Shirley May!
Shirley May. He knows her!
Sam, you gotta keep a level head,
Lu is right in there!
Oh, be quiet. Go call Dr. Brown,
Orange 3621.
All right, Sam.
It's alright, Lu, she works at the store.
She took an overdose of sleeping pills.
Is there something we can do
before the doctor gets here?
What happened, Mommy?
I don't know yet, dear.
You go get mommy's bed.
Uh... Lu, don't you think
you oughta get something on?
What is it,  Lu, what's so serious?
What is it?
He doesn't drink?
No, sometimes I wish he did.
Gamble?
No, but I'd prefer it to what he's doing.
He isn't in love with somebody else?
Yes.
Everybody!
He loves everybody!
He's in love with the human race, and...
animals, and birdlife and fish!
Why, he wouldn't even swat a fly!
Or any of those leeches who cling to him.
He just can't help helping people!
And that's bad?
Well... how does that affect your life?
What life?
Oh... all right...
You say marriage is a case
of give and take...
Well... he gives everything away,
and just have to take it.
He is so sorry for people...
He is his brother's keeper,
and he's got too many brothers.
He started with my brother,
and he's built up from there.
He wants a house by the side of the road,
"and to be a friend to man."
And I do the cooking!
Oh, don't look at me like that.
I know I sound like an idiot!
I know how I feel, but ...
when I say it, it just doesn't
come out right.
It sounds selfish,
but... there are other words,
like... wanting and wishing and...
yearning... and needing!
Lu... let's get one thing straight.
All peoples are agreed that there's
nothing greater than helping one another,
it's... the only way we can make
a happier world.
But- but you... you have a point.
Here I've been
selling this all my life,
and a man takes me up on it,
now his home's unhappy.
Well, there's no question but what the...
happiness of the home comes first.
Sam's a good father.
Do the... children suffer by his actions?
Oh, no, no.
He's a good father all right!
He's a good husband?
Well, he's got a blonde from the store in our
bed right now , if that's what you mean.
Oh no, no, it's perfectly harmless!
She just tried to commit suicide,
so he brought her in.
Well... maybe Sam's overdoing it a little.
I hope my sermon last Sunday
didn't cause him to go overboard?
Oh, no. No, that didn't start it.
It might have aggravated it a little...
but he's always been like that!
Even on our honeymoon.
He saw a man with his car stuck
in the mud,
wheels spinning.
My Sam jumps out, gathers twigs,
rips branches off trees and
shoves them under the wheels.
Then, for chains, he takes
the straps off our suitcases,
and wraps them around the tires.
Then, on his hands and knees,
covered with mud,
he says, "Now try it."
So the man put the car in reverse
and ran over him.
Then without even a word
of thanks or apology,
the man drove away!
With our straps!
Sam spent most of our honeymoon
in the Queen of the Angels Hospital.
That's when I learned to play the saxophone!
Now, you'd think that would be a lesson
to him about helping his fellow man.
But no!
Lu, you still love the big guy.
Give him another chance.
I'll talk to him.
Well...
I don't know exactly how to
put it to him,
I don't want to tell him to disregard
everything that I stand for, I...
I- I'm not sure just yet
how I'll tell him, but, uh...
I'll look up something on moderation.
Well, that... that might help.
What's the best way to see him,
how can I meet him "accidentally", huh?
Well, you could run into him casually
at the Athletic Club.
He takes a workout on his lunch hour.
If he hasn't given his trunks away!
We're having lamb chops for dinner.
What did you have for lunch?
Oh, salad! They make
a marvelous salad at the club.
And a glass of tomato juice.
Did you, uh... eat alone?
No, with Reverend Daniels.
I asked him what he was doing at the club,
and he said,
"A little exercise wouldn't hurt anybody."
He did. You know, there's a man
with a brilliant mind.
People just don't appreciate his wisdom.
More people should listen to
his sound advice.
Well, if you ask me,
I think he's a little mixed up.
I think he's having trouble
with his wife.
He is-... He is?
It's got so upset, I think
it's affecting his health.
So the poor man is gonna start
going to the club,
and exercise, and try to
get back into shape.
Oh... What did he say to you?
Well, he didn't say much of anything.
I did most of the talking.
He seemed so... troubled and...
unable to express himself.
I think it's serious, Lu.
You should have seen the look on his face
when I suggested that, uh...
that maybe you should go over
and have a little talk with his wife,
and try to straighten her out.
Yeah...
I said to him that...
you'd gone through a few things
with... with me, in a small way...
but you are so level-headed!
I knew something was wrong
when he said:
"Our wives' happiness is the only
important consideration."
He said, "We must give up whatever
is necessary to achieve that."
And you had an answer for that?
No. I asked him a question.
How much does a wife expect a man
to give up?
Should he ask her every time
before he makes a decision?
How much of his own judgement
should he rely on?
And how often should he run to her?
If he ran to her all the time, she wouldn't want him,
because he had no judgement.
I mean, if he's going to drop a dime
into a beggar's hat,
does he have to run to the telephone first,
and spend a nickel of it
to ask her permission?
That's silly.
- I should say.
My point is,
if he's gonna keep giving things up,
why doesn't he give up his self-respect,
and just give up?
She knew what he was
before she married him.
She knew what she was getting into,
didn't she?
Poor Mrs. Daniels.
My new home.
We'll take it!
Wait till you see the inside.
Come on, Sam.
Isn't this beautiful?
And look at that view!
Sam ...
ask Mrs. Nelson how much it is.
And don't quibble!
You won't have any trouble with him.
It's not bad, you know...
Another fireplace! And it's real!
Hey, you're making it
awfully tough for me!
Oh, I've never seen anything
like it. Have you?
Agree.
And we won't even have
to change the wallpaper!
What's the matter?
Bed too small for you?
- Little short, huh?
- Little.
We'll put a leaf in.
Oh, Sam... look behind you.
This is paradise!
When I think of my dressing table,
I can't bear to look at myself in this thing.
Sam, what's holding us up?
Why didn't you close the deal on the spot?
- Oh, you just can't do things that way.
- You can't?
Well, she promised to hold it.
Well, I hate to think of waiting
even 24 hours!
What are we waiting for?
We've got over 5,000 in the house fund.
Sam, we'll never find a place
more beautiful!
And I promise you, I'll cut expenses.
In every conceivable way.
And don't give me a Christmas present,
not a thing!
This is the greatest present
you could ever give me!
This is the present of my life!
Guess who was here and left a note for you.
Mr. and Mrs. Adams,
that lovely little couple
used to live next door.
I miss her.
How time flies!
You know, they've been gone
about eight months now,
and she's big as I am!
If it's a boy, they gonna call it Samuel.
And if it's a girl, Lucile.
They couldn't wait, that's the reason
why they left you that note.
- Thank you, Chloe.
- You're welcome.
Is it confidential, Sam,
or is it money?
Thirty-nine dollars and fifty cents.
What are they sending you money for?
Well...
Last summer, when you were away,
I spent some time with them
and they had a problem.
Oh, and what did good Sam do?
He said, "Look no further.
I sold everything."
"Here's your 39.50"
Alright. So you loaned them money
and they paid you back. That's nice!
Lu...
They were worried about
whether or not to have the baby.
Which, they are now going to have!
Well, things were bad for him,
no money and no work.
And they had a chance to
grab a spot on Highway 72 ...
where a lot of trucks go by.
It's a wonderful intersection, Lu,
and they're doing very well.
On 39.50? What have they got,
a portable peanuts stand?
Oh, no, a gas station.
There's a lot of money in it, of course
it takes time to get established...
How much did you give them?
It's a triple intersection, Lu.
You see, 72 and another one here ...
Sam, please.
Oh, don't worry.
They'll pay us back.
You can't guess how many trucks go by.
We sat there and clocked them,
and you'd be surprised.
How many do you think?
How much did you give them?
Oh... Well, they'd have paid us back sooner, only...
behind the gas station they built
a little, tiny...
A home?
Yeah, but... it's nothing you'd like...
Sam, you've given away
the whole house fund.
- Lu, these people are really worthwhile, dependable...
- Oh, Sam!
Oh, uh... let me- let me explain it, honey.
Darling... You do believe babies
should be born, don't you?
Don't throw their baby in my face!
No wonder you wanted 24 hours.
What good'll that do?
It's more like 24 years!
What's the baby do,
sell papers and pay us back?
Oh, Sam!
Why can't people stand on their own
two feet and have babies?
Well, I- I know it seems wrong not to have
discussed with you first, but...
this was an emergency, and you were
down in the country with your mother ...
Before telephones, Sam?
The bank wouldn't give it to them because...
well, they had no credit, and...
well, I thought they'd pay me back...
before, only...
- Before I found out.
I'm fed up with your helping
people behind my back!
You are nothing but a double-crossing,
two-faced, sneaking Samaritan!
Lu...
They're good people.
And they were desperate.
Oh, shut up!
Go away and leave me alone!
Well, you'll feel different
after she had the baby.
So will she!
Well... this is a pleasant surprise.
I thought I'd drop by, and see
how the Claytons were getting along
this fine Sunday afternoon.
Well, come in.
Well, I watched you two out of
the corner of my eye this morning,
and was delighted to see you both
looking so serenely happy.
Yeah, we're happy.
Hey, how are you and your wife
getting along now? Any better?
Yes. I don't think we'll have
any more trouble.
I told her about our little talk, Sam.
Did a lot of good.
She saw your point.
I told her what you said about
dropping a dime in a beggar's hat,
made her laugh.
Well, that's fine.
There'll be no need for Lu
straightening her out now.
No, no, I... don't think
that'll be necessary.
We both arrived to the realization that
so many domestic squabbles are silly.
Each has to give a little,
and see the other's viewpoint.
A... simple discussion of the problem,
and it blows away like, uh...
Boulder Dam, huh?
Reverend Daniels.
Do you believe in women having babies?
Well, I don't know who else, uh...
Well, under the right circumstances, yes.
Well, that's what I thought.
So I the couple next door some money.
You, soft-hearted, sad...
You- you, public benefactor, you at-
Hello, Reverend Daniels.
- Hello.
- It's always a pleasure to see you.
Well, I just stopped by,
on behalf of a very worthy cause.
It's... something that Sam and I, uh...
and he thought that you
would be interested too.
It's, uh... uh... uh...
What, something that slips
your mind at the moment?
Bundles for midgets, maybe?
No!... No...
It's, uh... a charity bazaar.
And Sam has volunteered your services
as a gypsy fortune teller.
He- He is going to be a sideshow barker.
Oughta raise a lot of money telling fortunes.
Show her the pretty costume
that you got for her, Sam.
- No, you show her.
- Oh, no, go ahead!
- No, here!
- Me?
Well, it's really... a very nice costume.
There.
Now, isn't that a pretty costume?
You'll be perfect as a gypsy!
Yeah.
Gypsies have no home, have they?
Good night, Chloe.
- And after this you, kids, get home earlier.
- We will.
- Good night, Chloe.
- See you tomorrow!
Hey, before we go in,
would you like fifteen minutes more
of what I think of you?
Well, I'd like it, Claude,
but it's awfully late.
Look, it's only six o'clock in Australia.
Come on, sit down, please.
Alright.
You ought to make the most of these moments,
when you're with me.
No, we better not, Claude.
Your sister won't like it.
Never mind my sister!
And what did I leave off?
Your hair, your eyes, your lips...
And that sunny smile!
- Oh, stop!
Did I say I'd walk a million miles
for one of those smiles?
Did I say I'd climb the highest mountain?
Swim some place too.
And I got you under my skin?
And, uh...
Are you impressed?
I like you very much, Claude, but...
The Claytons have been wonderful to me,
and I don't think they'd approve of this.
You see, you don't really know me
very well.
Well, I'm trying to find out,
the best I can!
Who is that?
Uh-oh, we're trapped.
Don't make a move.
Fixing some coffee, hmm?
I thought it'd be a good idea.
I think we'll be up a little late tonight.
You didn't say a word on the way home.
I thought you were having a good time,
you danced a lot with H.C.
You're doing alright, too.
Sam, H.C.'s offered me my old job back.
He wants me to go to Europe in the spring
on a buying trip.
That is, of course, with your approval.
It is a golden opportunity to put
some money away and...
I'll only be gone three or four months.
You can forget it!
- So that's your attitude!
- You're darn right it is!
Well, I don't understand why you mind,
you hardly ever see me anyway.
If I go, you can do as you please.
Maybe I'm holding you back.
Think of how many more
organizations you could join.
If I take this job, I get a
complete wardrobe furnished.
Unlimited expense account,
and a fine salary.
I'm going to Europe!
Well, I don't blame you for feeling that way,
I don't want you working!
- Oh, you don't, huh?
- No.
I suppose it's alright to go ahead with
the salary you earn and give away, but...
Sam, if we're ever going to have a home...
I know how much the house
meant to you.
Oh, it's not just the house,
it's everything!
All these problems you
brought into my life.
I'm losing my mind, they'll be
dropping a net on me!
Problems? What, for instance?
"Problems? What, for instance?"
Well, Shirley May, for instance.
You brought this department store Magdalene
into our house,
and how did she repay our kindness?
By trying to put her hooks into my brother!
Oh, I'll admit Claude's no angel,
but I can assure you,
I'm not going to stand aside
and see him wind up
with that alley-cat.
My mother would turn over in her grave.
- She would, huh?
- Yes.
And any girl who tries
to commit suicide
because a married man gets tired
of paying her expenses
and tosses her out on her ear,
is hardly the catch of the season!
Even for my brother!
Listen, I know your brother
better than you do.
He might be better off
with a couple of hooks in him.
- Oh...
- She marrying him is
like her jumping out of the frying pan
into your family!
Don't change the subject!
Are you going to ask her to get out,
or am I?
And...
Claude...
I'm sorry you had to hear it all this way.
Somehow I planned to tell you
in my own words,
a little differently.
I probably would have left myself
down a lot easier.
Now look what you made me say!
Me?
- Good evening.
- Hello there.
We are Mr. and Mrs. Adams.
Used to be next door neighbors.
Well, won't you come in?
Thank you. You heard what the
man said. Come on, little mother.
Take it easy now, take it easy.
We're old friends of the Claytons.
And we're a little high.
- Not me, he's been drinking my drinks too.
You may not know, but Sam Clayton is the
dearest friend I've got.
You know, if it weren't for Sam,
my wife wouldn't be having a baby.
Ah, here they are!
I give you our dear friends,
and benefactors...
Two hearts of gold
in three quarter time.
Come on, little gypsy.
Don't you like to waltz?
What have we got to waltz about?
We're celebrating, Mrs. Clayton.
We've had a few drinks.
- Ah, ah!
- I mean, I had the drinks.
What have you been drinking? Gasoline?
Wouldn't they buy it?
They not only bought all of the gasoline,
they bought the whole station!
Sam, I tell you, it's unbelievable.
A guy pulls into the station,
and he says "Fill'er up!".
He says that he likes me.
He says he's been watching me on the corner,
and counting the trucks going by.
In short, he'd like to purchase
my growing business.
I think he probably noticed
the way we're "expanding".
He wanted some air.
- Who's this?
- Claude.
- How are you?
- Glad to know you.
Out of the clear sky he says,
"Bud, what do you want for the station?"
Without laughing I says, "12,500, with
the little house in the rear thrown in."
And without laughing he says,
"I'll take it."
And it's his.
And here's your share!
I made it out for a thousand more.
Oh, no, you shouldn't-
Don't argue, we both did alright
on that deal, thanks to both of you.
I bought another place up the line.
You're in on that too, if you want.
Believe me, if I can ever do you a favour...
Well, you could give Claude a job,
he'll sell a lot of gas for you.
He's got one! Here, look me up, Claude.
- Good.
- Now, you want to celebrate?
Wanna dance the night away?
Ha- Hardly in the mood for that...
Well, pardon the intrusion.
Come on, little mother.
I think I'll go along.
No use getting stiff, you know.
Lu,
somebody paid us back.
I'm glad for a l- a lot of reasons.
I'm glad for them, and I'm glad for myself.
Kinda... renews your faith in people.
You know, it's... funny, Lu, we're so close
in so many ways,
and yet we seem to differ on things
that I think are important...
I wish we'd get together on...
what is really valuable in life.
I find happiness in different things
than you do.
I guess I did go overboard in...
helping them, and not thinking
about you and your home.
And I realize both are important.
But... you weren't there when I
talked to the two of them.
It seemed so right to tell them they
must have the baby,
and they'd regret it the rest of their lives
if they didn't
Years later they'd find themselves saying,
"He'd be sixteen now..."
Well, that's about it.
The house seemed awfully unimportant
at that moment.
Maybe... Maybe I'm unbalanced
and my scales need adjusting,
but when I... when I put some things on one side
and material things on the other
my scales go this way.
Gosh. I'll never change, Lu,
because that's the way I am.
So... while you're in Paris...
Who's going to Paris?
Well... thanks again for everything.
I'll be alright, Mr. Clayton.
I'm going to stay with Ruthie.
Lu, we made a profit on people...
Now we can buy the house, and...
maybe live happily ever after, hmm?
Claude, I feel badly enough now.
Why don't you go home to your sister,
she's told you all about me!
That's probably my sister now.
She told me she was coming over to see you.
Oh, no. No, Claude. I don't want to
see your sister.
Why not?
Well...
Why not? It would be nice to people.
She shot off her big mouth,
and she's sorry.
She just wants to tell you so.
Come on... Give her a break.
Come on in, sis.
I just came by to show her
my new uniform.
Tell her I love her,
and all she has to do is set the date.
Lu, you can take it up from there
as to what she needs.
Flowers, the right clothes,
you know all about those things.
And make her look lovely, Lu.
You know, after all, I couldn't be seen
with a dowdy bride.
Good bye.
May I sit down?
Is there something else wrong with me?
Didn't you say it all yesterday?
What else is on your mind? Say it!
I was just wondering if my wedding dress
could be altered to fit you.
I think it could.
Oh, that is, of course, if you like blue.
Oh, it would go wonderfully
with your hair and eyes.
And I would be more than happy
if you'd wear it.
I could bring it over,
and you could try it on, huh?
Oh, but... you'll have some
ideas of your own.
You'd look lovely in white too.
Oh, I love blue.
Mrs. Clayton, I will make your brother
the best wife a man ever had.
But I want to straighten you out about me.
I'm not really as bad as you think I am.
Oh, please, please don't.
Come on, let's talk about shoes.
I know exactly where to buy them,
believe me.
And... oh...
Oh, yes.
The hat!
I love your brother so much!
Oh, I do too. But I want to warn you,
you're marrying a screwball.
I know, but I understand it.
- You do?
- Yes.
I guess we have two of the most
wonderful men in the world.
I know I have.
But you can speak for yourself.
I will admit that Claude's
a little different.
I guess...
Let's say that at the moment you have
the most wonderful husband in the world!
- Did you see the morning paper?
- No.
Look.
Hello there!
Well, hello, it's nice to see you.
Thank you.
- What have you been doing?
- I've been taking lessons on the 3rd floor.
Well, how- how are you doing?
How I'm doing?... Ha, look!
Argyle!
- Oh... Pretty!
You get the first pair.
What size do you wear?
- Um... eleven and a half.
I'll make them twelve.
You may grow a little,
they may shrink a little.
Mr. Clayton.
Here's the money from the
fourth and fifth floors.
They came through one hundred percent.
That's everybody...
Except Mr. Borden.
What goes on here?
You see, every year Mr. Clayton
gives a Christmas dinner for the destitute.
Everybody in the store contributes to it.
I must get in on this.
You know, I go to school here.
- Oh, thank you.
- Say...
With all that money,
you ought to get to the bank.
Before someone bumps you on the head.
- That's right where I'm going.
- Bye.
Hello, Mr. Clayton.
Joe, sorry to keep you waiting.
- All right.
- Where's the turkeys?
Over in the truck.
Three more loads coming.
Best bunch I ever raised, too.
Here's the bill.
Hey, you raised the price too!
Oh, well, feed and everything's
going up, you know.
Here, I have it all made out
except for the amount.
Thanks, Joe.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Clayton.
Well, merry Christmas!
- Thank you very much. The same to you.
- Call you next year!
Bye.
Here, more ice.
Say, I shouldn't be here.
What time-
Hey, she took my watch too!
What happened?
Well, all I know is that somebody
hit me on the head, from behind.
How'd she get you up here anyway?
She had a heart attack!
She said she didn't want me
to take her to the hospital.
She'd be all right if I brought her home,
so I brought her here.
I asked her if she'd had these spells before.
She said only after she lost the baby.
Oh, the baby...
What's the idea walking around
with all this money on you?
Haven't you got a bank?
Yeah, I-...
The bank...
Oh, yes, I've got to get to the bank!
Say, you did get a bump,
didn't you?
Feeling better?
Yeah, I feel fine...
You see, Al, the way it is,
I actually paid for the turkeys out of
the money I was supposed to buy a house with.
Now I've lost the employees' money,
I've got to raise quite a chunk of dough.
Is there no way the bank could
loan me enough?
Well, Sam, I'd like to help you,
but my hands are tied.
You're on too many people's notes now.
You were a bad risk
before this happened, and...
now you're in a terrible mess.
Yeah, I guess unless I can
think of something...
we've lost our new home.
Sorry I couldn't help you, Sam.
Have another drink.
Just one, I- I clunk up my head,
and it makes me.... woozy.
I'll have one with you.
So Sam, here's to hoping you somehow you...
have a very merry Christmas.
- Hey, will you clear the driveway for me?
- Sure.
Sam! Why home so early?
Oh darling, this is absolutely the
happiest day of my life!
And have I got news for you!
Guess what?
Lu... Where are they taking our-
our sofa!
Sam, listen, the Nelsons are letting us
move into the new house right now.
Isn't that wonderful?
Y- y- yeah...
Well, you look more surprised
than delighted, darling.
Oh, Sam, you've been right, and
I've been wrong about so many things.
- I have?
Lu, where are they taking our...
That's what I mean.
I gave all the furniture away!
You gave the furniture away?
Well, stop them Lu!
Why? Oh, look, Sam.
Now it can be told.
I'm sick of looking at it.
I'm tired of every piece.
The second-hand dealers
would give us little to nothing,
so I called the Salvation Army.
Why not give it to them?
I felt that's what you'd want me to do.
It will help brighten some
poor family's Christmas,
help make it as merry
as our is going to be.
Oh... What's the matter, darling?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. What made you say that?
You've been working too hard.
That annual Christmas dinner
must be an awful headache!
Yes, it is. You're... giving...
everything away, huh?
Sure. And I got another
big surprise for you!
Another surprise?
- Ready, Mrs. Clayton?
- Oh, be right with you.
Where are you going?
That's the other surprise.
We are going to have dinner tonight
in our own new home.
Chloe's out buying everything.
And it will consist of all your
favourite dishes, including me.
Oh, and don't come home till six thirty.
I want everything to be just right!
And to give you a rough idea,
dinner starts with a... surprise!
Flown in at great expense!
Good bye!
See you in paradise!
So you called up everybody
that owes you money.
Yeah.
- They wouldn't give you a dime, huh?
- No.
Well, they'll do it every time.
Everybody I asked said I couldn't
have picked a worse time.
"Glad to pay you, Sam, but not now."
Just when I need it!
"I'd love to pay you, Sam,
but you know what doctors' bills are."
"Just got on my feet,
when I broke my leg."
"Sorry, Sam, but three boys in the hospital..."
No, "three boys in the college..."
"... and my mother-in-law in a tent..."
Oxygen tent.
Oh!
"But don't you worry, you'll get it
if it's the last thing I ever do!
But not right now...
Not right now.
- "Can you wait till April?"
- Yeah, some April!
Yeah, people are all alike, Sam.
I know what you mean.
I wish I could help you, but...
I had a bookmaker in here taking bets,
and it was only last month that he
ran away with all the cash I had.
Must have been quite a blow
to your wife.
No, she ran with him.
Maybe I should buy you a drink.
Well, I could stand one right now, thanks.
Mrs. Clayton, you look gorgeous!
Yes, and I hope Mr. Clayton will forget
what it cost when he sees me in it.
He will.
Mommy, when will Daddy come home?
Any minute now, dear.
We're hungry, Mommy.
Oh, would you come on, show Mommy what
you're going to do when Daddy gets home?
- Come on, Chloe.
- Alright.
Backstage, everybody!
Be sure and start together now.
Remember your finish?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Yes.
All right, now here comes Daddy.
Good evening, Daddy dear,
we're glad you're here,
So nice to welcome you!
All of us and Chloe want
to show you we're glad to see you!
And now you'll be so glad to hear
we have some happy news for you,
Now that we have a better home,
we'll all be better too!
We'd better be better!
I didn't say anything, pardon me.
Right...
You- You know what Confucius said
about helping people?
Yeah, he- he says so many things,
he's got me all mixed up.
Well, he said-
Confucius fills me with confusion!
Everybody said it, I got a whole book
full of 'em at home.
There's an old Scottish proverb, says, uh...
"Do a man a good turn, and they'll
never forgi'e ya."
"Forgi'e" is "forgive" in Scottish.
Yeah, I know, I know... I saw Harry Lauder
at the Palace, back in, uh... 1917.
- Allow me to quote.
- Go ahead, go ahead.
"He who has drunk his fill
turns his back on the filly."
Well, I kind of like that, uh...
there's a guy that's been around!
Yeah. No, but that isn't right.
"He... He who has drunk his fill
turns his back on the well."
It's a little dull that way,
don't you think?
Well, maybe he worked late at the store, Lu.
Why didn't he telephone that?
Did Daddy know we were going to have
black raspberry ice cream?
No, dear. We were going to surprise him.
Do you think something
happened to him, Mommy?
Oh, no! No, your Daddy's all right.
Maybe he isn't.
- Even the Arabs warned me.
- Uh-huh?
They said, "Sam, do no good,
and you will suffer no ingratitude"
Look at the clothes they wear.
No pockets!
Ask an Arab for a buck, and he'll
silently fold up his tent and...
silently steal away.
Yeah.
How about a drink, pal?
Oh, no... On your way now, putty face.
Fall apart outside, will you?
Oh, I gotta have a drink.
I've had it tough, pals, believe me!
I've seen better days.
Well then, go ahead and live on your memory.
Now get out of here, will you?
Come on back, friend, I'll buy you a drink.
Oh, I don't get you, Sam.
There you go again!
But, Tom, there is some good in everybody.
Well, the only thing in him that's
any good is my whiskey.
Some people are less fortunate than we are.
All they need is a helping hand.
Oh, I do, do I?
I can't remember when I heard
a more stupid remark.
You're not really helping me, all you're
doing is bolstering your own ego.
So he bought me a couple of lousy drinks...
and now he feels good about it.
All warm inside.
I bet you feel better than I do!
Oh, why don't you get out of here,
you crumpled bum?
This guy has got his own troubles.
- He has got trouble!?
- Yeah!
- He's got trouble!
- Yes!
He's one of the upper ten!
He's got everything.
You can afford to be condescending.
Dressed in the height of fashion!
Look at his clothes. Look!
Look at mine!
Yeah, well, just keep that up,
and he'll give you his.
That I want to see, my friend!
That I want to see!
There's a lot of fine talk in this world,
but no action!
- No action?
- No action.
Well, you're gonna see
some action now, buddy!
That's what I want, action!
- Hey, what are you doing there?
- I'm gonna call a wagon and put that bug in jug!
No, no, don't...
Come back... bug!
Why don't you go to bed
and sleep it off?
There you go again.
Sitting there, bedecked in your royal
arrayments, and laughing inwardly...
For you know I have no home,
and no bed on which to rest my head!
- No?
- No.
- I didn't know that.
- That's right.
- Well, I'll get you one.
- All right.
You want me to sleep well, don't you?
Thanks. Now don't forget to give him
the shirt off your back.
I'll- I'll be back.
Don't drop him in here!
And get him out of that woodwork, will you?
Get him out of here!
- How do you do?
- How'd'do?
- I'm Mr. Drew from the bank.
- Yes, sir.
I'd like to see Mr. Clayton.
Well, it's a bad time to see him.
He ain't here.
- Well then, could I see Mrs. Clayton?
- Well...
- It's rather important.
- Uh-huh, yes, sir.
Well, you wait-... Oh, well,
why don't you better come in.
I feel that I'm directly responsible
for what happened.
I turned him down for a loan
because he had no security.
Then I got to thinking.
What kind of a world is this?
There must be something rotten somewhere
when a man like your husband
can't get a loan.
I'm not for revising the banking laws, but...
sometimes we should make an exception,
and take a good heart for security.
So rest assured,
this house is yours.
Oh, what wonderful news!
If only he were here!
I've made him feel that I wanted this
more than anything else in the world.
More than I wanted him.
Tommy! Tommy, my boy!
I want my stuff.
You've had enough now, Sam.
Go on home!
What am I gonna do with a guy like that?
Look at him now!
Come back here, will you?!
No, I want to be alone!
Am I gonna have trouble with you?
Not if you leave me alone!
Sam, you're a too nice a guy...
Who's a nice guy?
You are! Why, you haven't got
a mean streak in you!
- I haven't, huh?
- Well, I- Yes you have...
Give it to me, will you?
Give it to me, Sam.
Give me the...
From now on, I'm the meanest man in town!
Watch and see.
I'm commencing to believe it!
Watch the next person that comes up
for a helping hand. I'll...
The next character that comes up to me
with his hand out,
see what I do, I'll...
Oh, Sam!
Oh, sorry, miss.
I'm awful sorry.
He's a nice fellow when he's not drinking.
Come here.
He shouldn't have done that.
- Here, this will cover what's missing, maybe...
- Thank you.
Here, miss.
I wonder if you'll help me get
him out of here. Get him home.
- I'm sorry, miss.
- Don't.
Thank you. All right, Sam.
You're all right.
Mid pleasures and palaces
though we may roam,
Be it ever so humble
there's no place like home!
Home! Home! sweet, sweet Home!
There's no place like Home!
Be it ever so humble,
O why don't you go home?
Home, home, sweet...
We'll find a bed for him.
- Oh, gee, will you, lady?
- Yes.
Oh, that's great!
That's fine. Here, take this, and...
I hope it helps out.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Come on.
- Oh, wait a minute, he's tied off.
Take it away!
Hello, Chloe, where's Sam?
- Mr. Sam ain't here.
- Not here?
Hello, Lu!
Hi, Claude. Have a cigar!
And will you have a cigar... Father?
And you, sir, have a cigar.
- Lu is here.
A baby boy. Eight pounds.
Little Sam!
Isn't it wonderful?
Well, what's the matter?
Do you think we have enough babies?
- Sam Clayton is missing.
- No...
There's something's happened to him.
We're terribly worried.
Well, what could happen to Sam?
Everybody loved him, he had no enemies.
Why, he's to nice a guy to be missing.
Oh, he's bound to turn up.
Nobody would harm him!
Why, he took care of everybody.
And everybody will take care of him.
The world needs Sam Clayton!
So do I.
It's Sam!
Oh, no!
We found this address on him.
Is he your husband?
They're wonderful people, Lu!
Yes, dear.
I'm a failure, Lu.
I'm gonna join them!
You're much better off without me.
I'm no good for you, Lu.
You're still young and so attractive,
isn't she?
So are you, you big...
Oh, I've messed up our lives,
I just stumble along and...
You just stumbled into the vice-presidency
of the store!
Yes.
According to the
banker man here,
he's going to loan us the money,
so the house will be ours too.
That's right!
And he hasn't been drinking!
Did you hear that?
I- I'm not a failure!
Do you take successful people too?
Thank you so much!
You are wonderful people!
I'm so glad I
gave you all my furniture,
because you brought him home safely!
Furniture up on the waters, I always say.
Won't you all come in the house
and have a great big slug of-
Hot chocolate?
Hot chocolate!
No thanks, I think we'd better be going.
Merry Christmas to you!
Merry Christmas.
Hey, wait a minute.
Just one more song, huh?
Alright.
What will it be?
I know!
Let me call you "sweetheart"
I'm in love with you,
Let me hear you whisper
That you love me too
All right, I love you too.
- Keep the love light burning
- Glowing.
Glowing in your eyes so blue
Let me call you sweetheart
I'm...
www.moviesubtitles.org