( SonarPings)
Man:
1 3 meters. You should see it.
( SonarPings)
Okay, take her up
and overthe bow rail.
( OverRadio ):
Okay, Mir2, we're going overthe bow.
Staywith us.
( SonarPings)
( Mechanical Whirring)
Okay, quiet. We're rolling.
Seeing her coming out of
the darkness like a ghost ship
still gets me everytime--
To see the sad ruin
ofthe great ship sitting here
where she landed at 2:30
in the morning ofApril 1 5, 1 91 2
after her long fall
from the world above.
( ManSnickers)
You are so full ofshit, boss.
- ( Giggles)
- ( Mechanical Whirring)
( SonarPinging)
Man: Dive six-- Here we are again
on the deck of Titanic
21/2 miles down
3,821 meters.
The pressure outside is
31/2 tons per square inch.
These windows are nine inches thick
and ifthey go
it's sayonara
in two microseconds.
All right, enough
ofthat bullshit.
( Mechanical Whirring)
Just put her down on the roofof
the officer's quarters likeyesterday.
- Man: Sure.
- Man ( OverRadio ): Okay, Mir 2.
We have landed right on the grand
staircase. You guys set to launch?
Yeah, Brock-- Launching Dunkin now.
Go, Charlie.
- All right, tether out.
- Man: Tether out.
Man ( OverRadio ): Okay, Brock,
we're dropping down along the hull.
Rogerthat. Okay, drop down and go
into the first-class gangway door.
I wantyou guys working the D deck
reception area and the dining saloon.
Man ( OverRadio ):
Copythat.
- Tether out.
- Man: Tether out.
- Now left, left.
- I'm coming left.
Brock:
Snoop Dog is on the move.
We're headed down the stairwell.
Okay, Lewis, drop down to B deck.
A deck.
Lewis:
Give me some rope, Captain.
B deck-- get in there,
get in there.
Brock: Watch the doorframe.
Watch the doorframe.
- I see it. I got it.
- ( Bang)
( Mechanical Whirring)
- ( Cracking)
- We're good.Just chill, boss.
Brock:
Makeyourturn. Come around.
- Lewis: Cable out, Captain.
- Makeyourturn. Watch the wall.
Yeah, Brock,
we're at the piano,you copy?
Brock:
Okay, copythat.
Brock: Okay, right there.
Right there. That's it!
- That's the bedroom door.
- I see it. I see it.
We're in!
We're in, baby. We're there!
Brock: That's Hockley's bed.
That's where the son ofa bitch slept.
Lewis:
Oops, somebody left the water running.
Hey, hold itjust a second.
Go backto the right.
That wardrobe door--
get closer.
- You smelling something, boss?
- I want to see what's under it.
- Give me my hands, man.
- ( Mechanical Whirring)
All right.
- Take it easy, it might come apart.
- Okay.
Go, go, go, go.
Flip it over. Flip it over. Go.
Keep going, go, go, go.
Okay, drop it.
Oh, baby, baby,
areyou seeing this, boss?
It's payday, boys.
(ManSpeaking OverLoudspeaker)
( Cheering)
( lmitates Cash Register):
Ka-ching!
- We did it, Bobby.
- Lewis: Oh,yeah. Who's the man?
Who's the best, baby?
Say it. Say it.
You are, Lewis.
( SawBuzzingLoudly)
- Bobby, my cigar.
- Bobby: Right here.
( Cheering)
Brock:
Okay, crack her open.
( ManSpeaking OverLoudspeaker)
Shit.
No diamond.
You know, boss, this same thing
happened to Geraldo
and his career never recovered.
Turn the camera off.
Bobby: Brock, the partners
would like to know how it's going.
Hey, Dave, Barry, hi.
Look, it wasn't in the safe
but hey, hey,
don't worry about it.
There's still plenty
of places it could be.
Hell yes! Floor debris in the suite, the
mother's room, purser's safe on C deck.
-Jimmy Hoffa's briefcase.
- Brock: A dozen other places.
Guys, look,you'vejust got to trust
my instincts. I know we're close.
Wejust got to go through
a little process ofelimination.
Hang on a second.
- Let me see that.
- We might have something here, guys.
Where's the photograph
ofthe necklace?
We'll call you right back.
I'll be goddamned.
Reporter: Treasure hunter Brock Lovett
is best known forfinding Spanish gold.
It's okay.
I'll feed you in a minute.
Now he has chartered
Russian subs to reach
the most famous shipwreck
ofall: the Titanic.
He is with us live
via satellite
from the research ship Keldysh
in the North Atlantic.
- Hello, Brock.
- Brock: Hello, Tracy.
Everyone knows the familiar
stories of Titanic--
the nobility, the band playing
till the very end and all that.
But what I'm interested in
are the untold stories
the secrets locked deep
inside the hull of Titanic.
We're out here using
robot technology
to go further into the wreck
than anybody's ever done before.
Your expedition is at the center
ofa storm ofcontroversy
over salvage rights
and even ethics.
Many are callingyou
a grave robber.
Nobody called the recovery ofartifacts
of King Tut's tomb "grave robbing."
- Woman: What is it?
- Turn that up, dear.
I have museum-trained experts
out here making sure
that these relics are preserved
and catalogued properly.
Take a look at this drawing
that we foundjust today:
A piece of paperthat's been
underwaterfor 84 years
and myteam were able
to preserve it intact.
Should this have remained unseen at
the bottom ofthe ocean for eternity?
I'll be goddamned.
Man (Over Loudspeaker):
Vnimanye, vnimanye...
Bobby: Brock!
There's a satellite call foryou.
Bobby, we're launching. You see
these submersibles going in the water?
Trust me, buddy.
You want to take this call.
This better be good.
You got to speak up.
She's kind ofold.
Great. This Brock Lovett.
- How can I helpyou, Mrs.--
- Calvert. Rose Calvert.
Mrs. Calvert?
I wasjust wondering ifyou had found
the Heart ofthe Ocean yet, Mr. Lovett.
Told you you wanted
to take the call.
All right,you have
my attention, Rose.
Can you tell us who the woman
in the picture is?
Oh,yes.
The woman in the picture is me.
( Yelling OverEngineNoise):
She's a goddamned liar--
Some nut case seeking
money or publicity.
God only knows why, like that
Russian babe, Anesthesia.
They're inbound!
Rose Dewitt Bukater died on the Titanic
when she was 1 7, right?
- That's right.
- Ifshe had lived, she'd be over 1 00.
1 01 next month.
Okay, so she's a very old
goddamned liar.
Look, I've already done
the background on this woman
all the way backto the '20s
when she was working as an actress.
An actress! There's
yourfirst clue, Sherlock.
Her name was Rose Dawson backthen.
Then she marries this guy named Calvert.
They move to Cedar Rapids
and she punches out a couple of kids.
Now, Calvert's dead, and from what
I hear, Cedar Rapids is dead.
And everybodywho
knows about the diamond
is supposed to be dead
or on this boat, but she knows.
Doesn't exactly
travel light, does she?
Mrs. Calvert, I'm Brock Lovett.
Welcome to the Keldysh.
Okay, let's get her
inside there.
- Hi, Ms. Calvert.
- Hi.
Welcome to the Keldysh.
Man:
Hey. Hey!
- ( Knocking)
- Rose: Yes?
- Areyour staterooms all right?
- Rose: Oh,yes, very nice.
Haveyou met
my granddaughter Lizzie?
She takes care of me.
We metjust
a few minutes ago.
Remember, Nana, up on deck?
There, that's nice.
Have to have my pictures
when I travel.
Can I getyou anything?
ls there anythingyou'd like?
Yes.
I would like to see my drawing.
Brock:
Louis XVI wore a fabulous stone
that was called
the Blue Diamond ofthe Crown
which disappeared in 1 792
about the same time old Louis
lost everything from the neck up.
The theory goes that
the crown diamond was chopped, too
recut into a heart-like shape that
became known as "Heart ofthe Ocean."
Today it would be worth more
than the Hope Diamond.
It was a dreadful, heavything.
I onlywore it this once.
Lizzie:
You actuallythinkthis isyou, Nana?
It is me, dear.
Wasn't I a dish?
I tracked it down
through insurance records--
An old claim that was settled
underterms ofabsolute secrecy.
Can you tell me
who the claimant was, Rose?
I should imagine
someone named Hockley.
Brock: Nathan Hockley, that's right.
Pittsburgh steel tycoon.
Claim was for
a diamond necklace
his son Caledon
bought his fiancee--you
a week before
he sailed on Titanic.
It was filed right
afterthe sinking
so the diamond had to have
gone down with the ship.
You see the date?
"April 1 4, 1 91 2."
Which means ifyour grandmother is
who she says she is
she was wearing the diamond
the daythe Titanicsank.
And that makesyou
my new best friend.
These are some ofthe things
we recovered from your stateroom.
This was mine.
How extraordinary!
And it looks the same as it did
the last time I saw it.
The reflection
has changed a bit.
( GaspsQuietly)
Areyou readyto go
backto Titanic?
Lewis: Okay, here we go. She hits
the berg on the starboard side, right?
She kind of bumps along punching holes
like Morse code-- dit-dit-dit--
along the side,
below the waterline.
Then the forward compartments
start to flood.
Now as the water level rises, it
spills overthe watertight bulkheads
which unfortunately
don't go any higherthan E deck.
So now as the bow goes down,
the stern rises up
slow at first, then faster
and faster until finally
she's got herwhole ass is sticking
up in the air and that's a big ass.
We're talking
20,000, 30,000 tons, okay?
And the hull's not designed to deal
with that pressure, so what happens?
She splits,
right down to the keel
and the stern
falls back level.
Then as the bow sinks, it pulls the
stern vertical and finally detaches.
Now, the stern sectionjust
kind of bobs there like a cork
for a couple of minutes, floods and
finally goes under about 2:20 a.m.
two hours and 40 minutes
afterthe collision.
The bow section planes away
landing about a halfa mile away
going 20, 30 knots when
it hits the ocean floor.
( lmitates Crashing)
Pretty cool, huh?
Thankyou forthat fine
forensic analysis, Mr. Bodine.
Ofcourse,
the experience of it was
somewhat different.
Will you share it with us?
( Music Playing)
( Crying)
- I'm taking herto rest.
- No.
- Come on, Nana.
- No!
Tape recorder.
Tell us, Rose.
It's been 84 years.
It's okay.Just tryto remember
anything-- anything at all.
Doyou want to hearthis
or not, Mr. Lovett?
It's been 84 years...
and I can still smell
the fresh paint.
The china had never been used.
The sheets had never
been slept in.
Titanicwas called
"The Ship of Dreams"
and it was, it reallywas.
Man: All third-class passengers
with a forward berth
this way, please, this queue.
- Right here.
- Big boat, huh?
- Daddy, it's a ship.
- You're right.
( CarHorn Tooting)
I don't see what
all the fuss is about.
It doesn't look any bigger
than the Mauritania.
You can be blase about some things,
Rose, but not about Titanic.
It's over 1 00 feet longerthan
Mauritania and far more luxurious.
Your daughter is fartoo difficult
to impress, Ruth.
So this is the ship
they say is unsinkable.
It is unsinkable.
God Himselfcould not sinkthis ship.
Sir,you have to check
your baggage through the main terminal.
- It's round that way, sir.
- I put myfaith in you, good sir.
- Now, kindly see my man.
- Yes, sir, my pleasure, sir.
- If I can do anything at all.
- Oh,yes, right.
All the trunks
from that carthere
1 2 from here, and the safe...
to the parlor suite,
rooms B-52, 54, 56.
- ( Whistle Blowing)
- Ladies...
better hurry.
( People Saying Good-byes)
- My coat?
- Woman: I have it.
Man: All third-class passengers
due here for a health inspection.
All third-class passengers
due here for health inspection.
Head up.
Welcome aboard, ma'am.
Welcome to Titanic.
Rose: It wastheShip ofDreams
to everyone else.
To meit wasaslave ship
takingmeback toAmerica
in chains.
Outwardly, I waseverything
a well-brought-up girlshouldbe.
Inside, I wasscreaming.
( Steam Whistle Blows Loudly)
( SpeakingSwedish )
Jack,you are pazzo.
You bet everything we have.
When you got nothing
you got nothing to lose.
Sven?
All right, moment oftruth.
Somebody's life's about to change.
Fabrizio?
-Niente.
- Ola?.
- Nothing.
Sven?
Uh-oh. Two pair.
I'm sorry, Fabrizio.
Che"sorry?" Ma vaffanculo!
You bet all the money.
I'm sorry,you're not going to see
your mom again for a long time
because we're going to America.
- Full house, boys.
- Whoa!
- Yeah!
-Dio mio, grazie!
( Cursingln Swedish )
- Come on.
- Figlio diputtana!
- I'm going home!
- ( Cursingln Swedish )
- I'm going home.
- I go to America.
Man: No, mate. Titanic
go to America in five minutes.
- Come on. Come on. Here.
- Fabrizio: Andiamo.
We're riding in high style now.
We're a couple of regular swells.
We're practically goddamn royalty,
ragazzo mio.
Fabrizio:
You see, it's my destino!
Like I told you,
I go to America to be milionario.
- Driver: Whoa, whoa!
- Bastardo!
- You're pazzo!
- Maybe, but I've got the tickets.
- Come on, I thoughtyou were fast.
- Aspetta!
Wait, wait! Hey, wait!
We're passengers. Passengers.
Haveyou been through
the inspection queue?
Ofcourse.
Anyway, we don't have any lice.
- We're Americans, both of us.
- Right, come aboard.
We're the luckiest sons of bitches
in the world,you know that?
( Ship's Horn Blares)
Good-bye!
- You know somebody?
- Ofcourse not. That's not the point.
Good-bye! I'll missyou!
Good-bye! I'm going
to neverforgetyou.
( Crowd Cheering)
All the way, darling.
360, 360.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Oh, right here.
Hey, howyou doing?
Jack. Nice to meetyou.
I'mJack Dawson.
Nice to meetyou.
Howyou doing?
Who saysyou get the top bunk?
( SpeakingSwedish )
This isyour private
promenade deck, sir.
Would you be
requiring anything?
- Hmm.
- Excuse me.
- Woman: This one?
- Rose: No. It had a lot offaces on it.
This is the one.
Would you like
all ofthem out, miss?
Yes, we need a little color
in this room.
Put it in there,
in the wardrobe.
God, not those finger paintings again.
They certainlywere a waste of money.
The difference between Cal's taste
in art and mine is that I have some.
They're fascinating, like being
inside a dream or something.
- There's truth, but no logic.
- What's the artist's name?
- Something Picasso.
- "Something Picasso."
He won't amount to a thing.
He won't, trust me.
- Put the Degas in the bedroom.
- At least theywere cheap.
Ah, put it in the wardrobe.
AtCherbourg, a woman came
aboardnamedMargaretBrown.
We all calledherMolly.
Historywould callher
"the Unsinkable MollyBrown. "
Well, I wasn't about to wait
all dayforyou, sonny.
Here,you thinkyou can manage?
Herhusbandhadstruckgold
someplace out West
andshe was whatmothercalled
"newmoney. "
By thenext afternoon, we were steaming
westfrom the coastoflreland
with nothing outaheadofus
butocean.
Take herto sea, Mr. Murdoch.
- Let's stretch her legs.
- Yes, sir.
- All ahead full, Mr. Moody.
- Very good, sir.
- ( Bells Ringing)
- ( BelIRings)
- All ahead full.
- Man ( Shouting): All ahead full!
Come on, lads. Get moving.
What's the reading?
( Crew TalkingAndShouting)
All right,
let's stoke them right up!
We're going full ahead!
21 knots, sir.
Hey, look, look, look!
Look, look!
See it?
There's another one. See him?
Look at that one.
Look at himjump!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
I can see the
Statue of Liberty already!
Very small, ofcourse.
I'm the king ofthe world!
( WhoopingAnd Yelling)
( Whooping)
Man: She's the largest
moving object ever made
bythe hand of man
in all history.
And our master shipbuilder,
Mr. Andrews here
designed her
from the keel plates up.
Well, I may have
knocked hertogether
but the idea was Mr. Ismay's.
He envisioned a steamer so grand
in scale and so luxurious
in its appointments that its
supremacywould never be challenged.
And here she is
willed into solid reality.
Man:
Hear, hear.
You know I don't
like that, Rose.
She knows.
We'll both have the lamb, rare,
with very little mint sauce.
Hmm,you like lamb,
right, sweet pea?
Areyou going to cut her meat
for her, too, there, Cal?
Hey, uh, who thought
ofthe name "Titanic"?
- Was ityou, Bruce?
- Well,yes, actually.
I wanted to convey sheer size
and the size means stability
Iuxury, and above all,
strength.
Doyou know of Dr. Freud,
Mr. Ismay?
His ideas about the male
preoccupation with size
might be of particular
interest toyou.
- What's gotten intoyou?
- Excuse me.
- I do apologize.
- She's a pistol, Cal.
- Hopeyou can handle her.
- Well, I may have to start minding...
what she reads from now on,
won't l, Mrs. Brown?
Freud-- Who is he?
ls he a passenger?
( Man ExplainingPropeller
To Little Girl)
It makes these waves,
makes them spin.
Fabrizio:
The ship is nice, huh?
- Yeah, it's an lrish ship.
- Is English, no?
No, it was built in lreland.
1 5,000 lrishmen built this ship.
Solid as a rock.
Big lrish hands.
That's typical. First-class dogs
come down here to take a shit.
Uh, it lets us know where we rank
in the scheme ofthings.
Like we could forget?
- I'm Tommy Ryan.
-Jack Dawson.
- Hello.
- Fabrizio.
Hi. Doyou make any money
with your drawings?
Oh, forget it, boyo. You'd as like
have angels fly outyour arse
as get next
to the likes of her.
( Laughs)
- Doyou mind?
- I hopeyou're proud ofthis.
Isawmy whole life
asifl'dalreadylivedit--
an endlessparade
ofparties andcotillions
yachts andpolo matches
always thesamenarrowpeople,
thesamemindless chatter.
Ifelt likel wasstanding
atagreatprecipice
with no one topullmeback
no one who cared
oreven noticed.
- ( Woman Grunts)
- ( RoseSobbing)
( RunningFeetAndSobbing)
( TakingShort,
Anxious Breaths)
Don't do it.
Stay back.
Don't come any closer.
Come on.Just give meyour hand.
I'll pull you back over.
No! Staywhereyou are.
I mean it.
I'll let go.
No,you won't.
What doyou mean, no, I won't?
Don't presume to tell me what I will
and will not do. You don't know me.
Well,you would have
done it already.
You're distracting me.
Go away.
I can't. I'm involved now.
You let go and I'm going to have to
jump in there afteryou.
Don't be absurd.
You'll be killed.
- I'm a good swimmer.
- The fall alone would kill you.
- It would hurt.
- I'm not saying it wouldn't.
To tell you the truth
I'm a lot more concerned
about that water being so cold.
( ShoeDrops To Deck)
- How cold?
- Freezing.
Maybe a couple degrees over.
You ever, uh...
ever been to Wisconsin?
What?
Well, they have some
ofthe coldest winters around.
I grew up there
near Chippewa Falls.
I rememberwhen I was a kid,
me and myfather, we went ice fishing
out on Lake Wissota.
Ice fishing is,you know,
whereyou--
( Angrily):
I know what ice fishing is!
Sorry.
Youjust seem like,you know,
kind ofan indoor girl.
Anyway, l, uh...
I fell through some thin ice
and I'm tellingyou...
waterthat cold,
like right down there
it hitsyou like a thousand knives
stabbingyou all overyour body.
You can't breathe,
you can't think--
at least not about anything
but the pain.
Which is why I'm not looking forward
tojumping in there afteryou.
Like I said...
I don't have a choice.
I guess I'm kind of hoping
you'll come back overthe rail
and get me offthe hook here.
You're crazy.
That's what everybody says,
but with all due respect, miss
I'm not the one hanging off
the back ofa ship here.
Come on.
Come on, give meyour hand.
You don't want to do this.
Whew!
I'mJack Dawson.
Rose Dewitt Bukater.
I'm going to have to getyou
to write that one down.
Come on.
- ( Screams)
- ( Grunting)
I gotyou! Come on.
Come on!
( Screams)
Help! Please!
- Please get me!
- Listen. Listen to me.
I've gotyou. I won't let go.
Now pull yourself up. Come on.
( Grunts)
Come on. That's right.
You can do it.
I gotyou.
What's all this?
You stand back!
And don't move an inch!
- Fetch the master-at-arms!
- Care for a brandy?
Cal: This is completely unacceptable!
What madeyou think
thatyou could putyour hands
on myfiancee?
- Look at me,you filth!
- Cal...
- What doyou thinkyou were doing?
- Cal, stop.
- It was an accident.
- An accident?
It was. Stupid really.
I was leaning over,
and I slipped.
I was leaning far over
to see the, uh...
uh... uh...
the, uh... uh...
- Propellers?
- propellers and I slipped.
And I would have gone overboard
but Mr. Dawson here saved me
and almost went over himself.
You wanted to see...
She wanted to see the propellers.
Like I said,
women and machinery do not mix.
Was that the way of it?
Yeah. Yeah,
that was pretty much it.
Well, the boy's a hero then.
Good foryou, son. Well done.
So it's all's well
and backto our brandy, eh?
Look atyou. You must be freezing.
Let's getyou inside.
Perhaps a little something
forthe boy.
Ofcourse. Mr. Lovejoy,
I think a 20 should do it.
Is that the going rate
for saving the woman you love?
Rose is displeased.
What to do?
I know.
Perhapsyou couldjoin us
for dinnertomorrow evening
to regale our group
with...your heroic tale.
Sure, count me in.
Good. Settled then.
This should be interesting. Mmm.
( Whistles)
Can l, uh... bum a smoke?
You'll want to tie those.
It's interesting.
Theyoung lady slips so suddenly
and you still had time
to removeyourjacket
and your shoes.
- ( Music BoxPlaying Tune)
- ( KnockAtDoor)
( DoorOpens)
I knowyou've been melancholy.
I don't pretend to know why.
I intended to save this
until the engagement gala
next week.
But I thought tonight.
Good gracious.
Perhaps as a reminder
of myfeelings foryou.
- Is it a...
- Diamond? Yes.
56 carats to be exact.
It was worn by Louis XVI
and they called it
"Le CoeurDeLa Mer. "
Both:
The Heart ofthe Ocean.
Yes.
It's overwhelming.
Well, it's for royalty.
We are royalty, Rose.
You know, there's nothing
I couldn't giveyou.
There's nothing I'd denyyou
ifyou would not deny me.
Now open your heart
to me, Rose.
Jack: Well, I've been on my own since
I was 1 5 since myfolks died.
And I had no
brothers or sisters
or close kin in that part
ofthe country.
So I lit on out ofthere
and I haven't been back since.
You couldjust call me
a tumbleweed blowing in the wind.
Well, Rose...
we've walked about a mile
around this boat deck
and chewed over how great
the weather's been and how I grew up
but I reckon that's not why
you came to talkto me, is it?
- Mr. Dawson, l--
-Jack.
Jack...
I want to thankyou
forwhatyou did.
Notjust for... for pulling me back
but foryour discretion.
You're welcome.
Look, I know
whatyou must be thinking.
Poor little rich girl.
What does she know about misery?
No. No, that's not what
I was thinking.
What I was thinking was
what could have happened to this girl
to make herthink
she had no way out?
Well, l--
It was everything.
It was mywhole world
and all the people in it
and the inertia of my life
plunging ahead
and me, powerless to stop it.
God! Look at that thing.
You would have gone
straight to the bottom.
500 invitations have gone out.
All of Philadelphia society
will be there
and all the while
I feel I'm...
standing in the middle
ofa crowded room
screaming at the top of my lungs
and no one even looks up.
Doyou love him?
- Pardon me?
- Doyou love him?
You're being very rude.
You shouldn't be asking me this.
Well, it's a simple question.
Doyou love the guy or not?
This is not
a suitable conversation.
-Why can'tyoujust answerthe question?
-( Nervous Laughter)
This is absurd. You don't know me,
and I don't knowyou
and we are not having
this conversation at all.
You are rude and uncouth
and presumptuous and I am leaving now.
Jack. Mr. Dawson,
it's been a pleasure.
I soughtyou out to thankyou
and now I have thanked you...
- And you've insulted me.
- Well,you deserved it.
- Right.
- I thoughtyou were leaving.
- I am.
You are so annoying.
- ( Chuckles)
- Wait.
I don't have to leave.
This is my part ofthe ship. You leave.
Oh-ho-ho,
well, well, well.
Now who's being rude?
What is this stupid thing
you're carrying around?
So what areyou,
an artist or something?
Well, these are rather good.
They're, uh--
They're very good actually.
Jack, this is exquisite work.
They didn't thinktoo much
ofthem in old Paree.
Paris! You do get around
for a poor--
Well, uh, uh, a person
of limited means.
Go on, a poor guy,
you can say it.
Well, well, well.
And these were drawn from life?
Well, that's one
ofthe good things about Paris--
Iots ofgirls willing
to take their clothes off.
You liked this woman.
You used her several times.
Well, she had beautiful hands,
you see?
I thinkyou must have had
a love affairwith her.
No, no, no, no, no.
Just with her hands.
She was a one-legged prostitute.
See?
- ( Aghast): Oh!
- ( Both Chuckle)
Ah, she had a good sense
of humor, though.
Oh, and this lady...
she used to sit
at this bar every night
wearing every piece
ofjewelry she owned
just waiting
for her long-lost love.
Called her Madame Bijou.
See how her clothes
are all moth-eaten?
Well,you have a gift,Jack.
You do. You see people.
I seeyou.
And?
You wouldn't havejumped.
But the purpose of university
is to find a suitable husband.
Rose has already done that.
Look, here comes
that vulgar Brown woman.
Quickly, get up
before she sits with us.
Hello, girls. I was hoping
I'd catch you at tea.
We're awfully sorry
you missed it.
The countess and I werejust off
to take the air on the boat deck.
What a lovely idea.
I need to catch up on my gossip.
Molly:
Countess.
Soyou've notyet
lit the last four boilers?
No, I don't see the need.
We are making excellent time.
The press knows
the size of Titanic.
Now I want them to marvel
at her speed.
We must give them
something new to print.
This maiden voyage of Titanic
must make headlines.
Mr. Ismay, I would prefer
not to push the engines
until they've been
properly run in.
Ofcourse
I'mjust a passenger.
I leave it toyour good offices
to decide what's best.
But what a glorious end
toyourfinal crossing
ifwe were to get into New York
on Tuesday night and surprise them all.
Make the morning papers.
Retire with a bang, eh, E.J.?
Good man.
Well, afterthat I worked on
a squid boat in Monterey.
Then I went down to Los Angeles
to the pier in Santa Monica
and started doing portraits there
forten cents apiece.
Why can't I be likeyou,Jack--
just head out forthe horizon
whenever I feel like it?
Saywe'll go there
sometime to that pier
even ifwe only
everjust talk about it.
No, we'll do it.
We'll drink cheap beer. We'll ride
on the roller coastertill we throw up.
Then we'll ride horses on the beach
right in the surf.
Butyou'll have to do it like a real
cowboy. None ofthat sidesaddle stuff.
- You mean, one leg on each side?
- Yeah.
- Can you show me?
- Sure... ifyou like.
- Teach me to ride like a man.
- And chew tobacco like a man.
And spit like a man.
They didn't teach you that
in finishing school?
- No.
- Well, come on, I'll showyou.
Let's do it.
I'll showyou how. Come on.
Jack, no!Jack, no!
Wait,Jack. No,Jack.
I couldn't possibly,Jack.
Watch closely.
- That's disgusting!
- All right,yourturn.
That was pitiful!
Come on,you really got
to hawk it back,you know?
Get some leverage to it.
Useyour arms, arcyour neck.
( Hawks)
- See the range on that thing?
- Mm-hmm.
- ( RoseHawking)
-Jack: Okay, go.
( Hawks)
-That was better. You got to work on it.
-Really?
Reallytry and hawk it up
and get some bodyto it,you know?
You got to...
( Snorting)
( Swallows)
Mother.
May I introduceJack Dawson?
Charmed, I'm sure.
The others were gracious
andcurious
abouttheman
who hadsavedmylife
butmymotherlookedathim
likean insect--
a dangerous insect
which mustbesquashedquickly.
Well,Jack, sounds likeyou're a good
man to have around in a sticky spot.
( TrumpetPlayingFanfare)
Why do they always insist on announcing
dinner like a damn cavalry charge?
- ( Laughs)
- Shall we go to dress, Mother?
Seeyou at dinner,Jack.
Uh, son? Son!
Doyou have the slightest comprehension
whatyou're doing?
Not really.
Well,you're about to go
into the snake pit.
What areyou planning to wear?
I figured. Come on.
I was right.
You and my son
arejust about the same size.
Pretty close.
- ( Whistles)
- You shine up like a new penny.
( Laughs)
Good evening, sir.
( Orchestra Playing
"On TheBeautifuIBlueDanube")
Good evening.
Man:
Hello.
Cal: Doyou know that there are
several thousand tons
of Hockley steel
in this very ship?
- Ruth: Hmm. Which part?
- Cal: All the right ones, ofcourse.
Then we'll know who to hold
accountable ifthere's a problem.
- Where's my daughter?
- Oh, she'll be along.
- There is the countess.
- Hello, my dear.
- Good evening, Cal.
- Cal: So good to seeyou.
I saw that in a nickelodeon once
and I always wanted to do it.
( Snickers)
Ruth:
I'll seeyou at dinner.
Darling? Surely
you remember Mr. Dawson.
Dawson?
( Chuckles)
Well, it's amazing.
You could almost pass for a gentleman.
- Almost.
- Extraordinary.
Ruth:
My dear, it's delightful to seeyou.
What a remarkable
voyage this is.
- It's mad, isn't it?
- Ruth: I loveyour perfume.
There's the Countess of Rothes.
And, um, that'sJohnJacob Astor--
the richest man on the ship.
His little wifeythere, Madeleine,
is my age and in delicate condition.
See how she's
trying to hide it?
- Quite the scandal.
- Hmm.
And that's Benjamin Guggenheim
and his mistress Madame Aubert.
Mrs. Guggenheim is at home
with the children, ofcourse.
And over here we have
Sir Cosmo and Lucille Lady Duff-Gordon.
She designs naughty lingerie,
among her manytalents.
Very popularwith the royals.
Congratulations, Hockley.
She's splendid.
Why, thankyou.
- Care to escort a ladyto dinner?
- Certainly.
- ( Chuckling)
- Sweat pea?
- Cal: Sweet pea.
- Ain't nothin' to it, is there,Jack?
Remember, they love money, sojust
pretend likeyou own a gold mine...
and you're in the club.
- Hey, Astor!
- Well, hello, Molly. Nice to seeyou.
J.J. Madeleine,
I'd likeyou to meetJack Dawson.
- How doyou do?
- Pleasure.
Hello,Jack.
Areyou ofthe Boston Dawsons?
No-- the Chippewa Falls Dawsons,
actually.
Oh,yes. Yes.
Hemusthave been nervous,
butheneverfaltered.
Theyassumed
he wasone ofthem--
Heir to a railroadfortune,
perhaps.
Newmoney, obviously,
butstilla memberofthe club.
Mother, ofcourse,
couldalways be countedupon.
Tell us ofthe accommodations
in steerage, Mr. Dawson.
I hearthey're quite good
on this ship.
The best I've seen, ma'am.
Hardly any rats.
( Laughter)
Mr. Dawson isjoining us
from the third class.
He was ofsome assistance
to myfiancee last night.
It turns out that Mr. Dawson
is quite a fine artist.
He was kind enough to show me
some of his worktoday.
Rose and I differ somewhat
in our definition offine art.
Not to impugn yourwork, sir.
( Clears Throat)
Ismay:
She may be mine on paper
but in the eyes ofGod,
she belongs to Thomas Andrews.
( Whispering):
Are these all for me?
Just start from the outside
and workyourway in.
He knows every rivet
in her, don'tyou, Thomas?
- Your ship is a wonder, truly.
- Thankyou, Rose.
- And how doyou takeyour caviar, sir?
- No caviarfor me, thanks.
Never did like it much.
And where, exactly,
doyou live, Mr. Dawson?
Well, right now, my address
is the R.M.S. Titanic.
Afterthat,
I'm on God's good humor.
And how is it
you have means to travel?
I work myway
from place to place--
You know,
tramp steamers and such.
But I won myticket
on Titanic here
at a lucky hand at poker.
A very lucky hand.
- All life is a game of luck.
- Mmm.
A real man makes
his own luck, Archie.
- Right, Dawson?
- Mmm.
And you find that sort of
rootless existence appealing, doyou?
Well,yes, ma'am, I do.
I mean, got everything I need
right here with me.
Got air in my lungs
and a few blank sheets of paper.
I mean, I love waking up in the morning
not knowing what's going to happen
orwho I'm going to meet,
where I'm going to wind up.
Just the other night, I was sleeping
under a bridge, and now here I am
on the grandest ship in the world
having champagne with you fine people.
- ( Laughter)
- I'll take some more ofthat.
I figure life's a gift,
and I don't intend on wasting it.
You never know what hand
you're going to get dealt next.
You learn to take life
as it comes atyou. Hereyou go, Cal.
To make each day count.
- Well said,Jack.
- Hear, hear!
To making it count.
- All: To making it count.
- Archie: Bravo.
( MollyLaughing)
Mr. Brown had no idea
I'd hidden the money in the stove.
( Laughter)
So he comes home drunk as a pig,
celebrating and he lights a fire.
( Laughter)
( Softly): Next it'll be
brandies in the smoking room.
Archie:
Well,join me in a brandy, gentlemen?
( MenAgree)
Now they retreat into a cloud ofsmoke
and congratulate each other
on being masters ofthe universe.
Ladies, thankyou for
the pleasure ofyour company.
Rose, may I escortyou
backto the cabin?
- No, I'll stay here.
- Hereyou go, Molly.
Archie:
Joining us, Dawson?
You don't want to stay out here
with the women, doyou?
No, thanks.
I've got to be heading back.
- Ah.
- Probably best.
It'll be all business
and politics, that sort ofthing--
Wouldn't interestyou.
But Dawson, good ofyou to come.
Jack, mustyou go?
Time for me to go row
with the other slaves.
Good night, Rose.
www.moviesubtitles.org