Mr. Lowe, man this boat.
Lowe:
Right, is everybody all right?
Nobody panic.
- Crewman: Stay back!
- We're too late.
There are more boats
down the front.
Staywith this one-- Murdoch.
He seems to be quite practical.
( WomenScreaming)
Lowe:
Sit down!
Stay back,you lot.
Stay back!
Stay back, the lot ofyou!
- ( Gunshots)
- It's starting to fall apart.
We don't have much time.
- Mr. Murdoch?
- Mr. Hockley.
You two, with me, now.
I'm a businessman, asyou know and I
have a business proposition foryou.
Crewman:
Easy now. All together.
Lower away, lower away.
Jack:
Come on, Rose.
The boats are gone!
Colonel, are there
any boats on that side?
No, miss, but there are a couple
of boats all the wayforward.
This way, I'll lead you.
( PlayingFinaIChord)
What's the use?
Nobody's listening to us anyway.
Well, they don't listen to us
at dinner either.
Come on, let's play. Keep us warm.
"Orpheus."
( PlayingFastMusic From
"Orpheus ln The Underworld")
Music to drown by.
Now I know I'm in first class.
- Where is everyone?
- They're all still aft, sir.
We have an understanding then,
Mr. Murdoch?
( EveryoneShouting)
( Gunshots)
Women and children only!
Get back!
Step back, sir. Come through, madam.
This way. Step back, sir.
You'd better check
the other side. Go!
Crewman: Any more women and children?
Any children?
I found her on the other side
waiting for a boat... with him.
- Any more women and children?
- They're all aboard, Mr. Murdoch.
Anyone else, then?
Anyone else? Hurry along.
Stand bythe falls.
( Softly):
Oh, goddamn it all to hell.
- Shit.
- Fire!
Sir! Sir,you can't
go through here.
Sir,you can't go through.
Yes,yes, splendid.
Right.
Murdoch:
Prepare to lower!
Ready on the left.
Take them down.
Keep it steady.
Both sides together, steady.
- Give herto me.
- Girl: Daddy.
Man: It'll be fine, darling.
Don'tyou worry.
It's good-bye for a little while.
Onlyfor a little while.
There'll be another boat
forthe daddies.
This boat's forthe mummies
and the children.
You hold Mummy's hand
and be a good little girl.
- I'm not going withoutyou.
- No,you have to go... now!
- No,Jack.
- Get in the boat, Rose!
- Yes, get on the boat.
Yes, get on the boat, Rose.
My God, look atyou.
You look a fright.
Here.
Put this on. Come.
- Go on, I'll get the next one.
- No, not withoutyou.
Jack: I'll be all right.
Listen, I'll be fine.
I'm a survivor, all right?
Don't worry about me.
-Jack: Now go on, get on.
- I have an arrangement with an officer
on the other side
ofthe ship.
Jack and I can get offsafely,
both of us.
See? Got my own boat to catch.
Cal:
Now, hurry. They're almost full.
- Step aboard, miss.
- Cal: Come on, hurry.
- Step aboard, please.
- Man: Be Daddy's good girl.
- Step lively.
- Crewman: Keep back, keep back, I say.
Clearthe row, please.
Lower away!
( Passengers Gasp )
Crewman:
Slowly. Keep going. Keep going.
And lower away evenly, lads.
Easy. Lower away.
- You're a good liar.
- Almost as good asyou.
Crewman:
Easy now... and lower away.
There's no, uh--
There's no arrangement, is there?
No, there is.
Not thatyou'll
benefit much from it.
I always win,Jack...
one way or another.
Crewman:
Easy. Even, lads.
Keep going, keep going.
- Rose!
- (Passengers Yelling)
- Stop her!
-Jack: Rose, what areyou doing?
- Cal: Stop her!
- No!
Rose.
You're so stupid.
Why'd you do that?
You're so stupid, Rose.
Why did you do that? Why?
Youjump, I jump, right?
Right.
Oh, God, I couldn't go.
I couldn't go,Jack.
It's all right.
We'll think ofsomething else.
- Rose: At least I'm with you.
- We'll think ofsomething.
Come on!
( Gunshot)
Come on, move!
- Come on.
- (Gunshot, RoseScreams)
Move!
- ( Gunshot)
- ( Screams)
Come on,
Come on, Rose. Come on.
-( Gunshot)
- Rose, come on!
- (Gunshot)
- Move, Rose!
- ( Gunshot)
- Go!
( Grunts ln Despair)
( MetaIGroaning)
I hopeyou enjoy
yourtime together.
( Chuckles)
What could possibly be funny?
I put the diamond in the coat.
And I put the coat on her!
Come on.
( Dishes Clinking)
( Child Yelling)
( Screaming)
We can't leave him.
All right, come on.
( Wailing)
( ChildScreaming)
Go back!
( Yellingln Czech )
It's the wrong way!
Come back!
( RoseAndJack Yelling
ForMan To Stop )
Go!
( Water Thundering)
-Jack!
- Rose!
( Groaning)
This way.
Come on. Give meyour hand.
Oh, God!
Help!
Rose:
Wait, sir,
open the gate, please. Please.
Please. Help us.
Please!
Bloody hell.
- Come on, come on!
- Come on!
- Go, go!
-Jesus.
Please. Come on. Hurry!
Come on!
I'm sorry,
I dropped the keys.
Wait! Please!
Don't leave, please!
Get more help! No!
I got them.
Which one is it, Rose?
The sharp one,
trythe sharp one.
Hurry,Jack.
- Oh, no!
- Hurry,Jack.
- It's stuck.
- Hurry.
- Hurry,Jack!
Hurry!
( Screaming)
I got it, I got it!
Go! Go, Rose!
Go, go!
Jack!Jack, come on!
Move, move!
Crewman:
Keep on rocking. Oars in place.
Get an oar under it.
Murdoch:
Women and children only, damn you.
Crewman:
Hold it, hold it.
( Men Yelling)
Get these davits cranked in.
Then get the falls hooked up.
Murdoch:
Stay back.
Child:
Help me.
( Crying)
Keep going up.
Murdoch:
Stop pushing!
Stay back!
Will you give us a chance to live,
you limey bastard?
I'll shoot any man who tries
to get past me. Get back!
- Bastard!
- Get back!
We had a deal, damn you.
Your money can't saveyou any more
than it can save me. Get back.
Crewman:
Women and children only!
( Gunshot)
( PassengersScreaming)
Tommy! No, Tommy.
Bastardo!
Oh, no, oh, no.
Oh, no. Oh, Tommy.
- No, Will!
- (Gunshot)
Stand back, damn you.
Get back, damn you.
( Screaming)
- ( Child Crying)
- I have a child.
- Cal: I have a child.
- Clear a path here.
Please, I have a child.
Please, I'm all she has
in the world.
Go on. Step back,
step back, I say.
- Please.
- Woman: Here, give herto me.
Give her here.
- ( Child Wailing)
- There, there.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mr. Andrews.
Oh, Rose.
Won'tyou even
make a tryfor it?
I'm sorrythat I didn't build you
a stronger ship,young Rose.
It's going fast.
We have to move.
Wait.
Good lucktoyou, Rose.
And toyou.
Mr. Guggenheim.
These are foryou, Mr. Guggenheim.
No, thankyou.
We are dressed in our best
and are prepared to go down
as gentlemen.
But we would like a brandy.
Capitan. Capitan,
where should I go? Please.
Crewman:
Captain! Captain, sir.
( Orchestra StilIPlaying)
Right, that's it, then.
Good-bye, Wally, good luck.
So long, old chap.
( BeginsPlaying
"NearerMy God To Thee")
(Joinsln )
( Orchestra StilIPlaying)
And so they lived
happilytogetherfor 300years
in the land ofTir Na Nog
the land ofeternal
youth and beauty.
( Playing
"NearerMy God To Thee")
( CrewmenAndPassengers
Yelling)
There's no time!
Cut those falls!
Cut them, cut them
ifyou have to!
Crewman:
I need a knife. I need a knife.
Cut her loose.
Cut those bloodyfalls.
( PlayingLastNotes OfSong)
Gentlemen,
it has been a privilege
playing with you tonight.
( People Screaming)
( Screaming)
We have to stay on the ship
as long as possible! Come on!
Jack:
This way. Overthe rail!
Come on.Jump!
Come on!
( Screaming)
( Gasping)
Jack:
I gotyou.Jump!
( Gasping)
I've gotyou, miss!
-Jack!
-Jack: Come on!
Cal:
Get back!
( CablesSnapping)
( MetaIGroaning)
No! You'll swamp us.
( HystericaIShrieking)
Yea, though I walkthrough
the valley ofthe shadow ofdeath...
You want to walk a little faster
through that valleythere?
( WildScreaming)
Row! Pull together!
( Screams)
Priest:
Holy Mary, mother ofGod
prayfor us sinners now and
at the hour ofour death, amen.
Hail Mary, full ofgrace
- the Lord is with thee.
- This way.
Jack:
Come on. Come on!
( Gasping)
I saw a new heaven
and a new earth
when the first heaven and
the first earth had passed away...
- ( WomenScreaming)
- and there was no more sea.
( Gasping)
- Woman: Help me!
- It'll be over soon.
It'll all be over soon.
Priest:
And He shall dwell with them
and they shall be His people
and God Himself
shall be with them...
Jack, this is where we first met.
And God shall wipe away
all the tears from their eyes
and there shall be
no more death.
Neither shall there
be sorrow or crying.
Neither shall there be
any more pain
forthe formerworld
has passed away.
( Shattering)
Bloody pull faster, and pull!
( People Screaming)
( Yelling)
- Man: Hang on, Miss Trudy!
- (Shrieking)
( Crashing, Shattering
AndRumbling)
( Yells)
( Screams)
Man:
Help me! Please, save me!
- Woman: Help!
-Jack: Hold on real tight!
( Shriekingln Distance)
( WomanSobbing)
( Terrible Screaming
And Yellingln Distance)
God Almighty!
Crewman:
Get those breakers in! Keep them in!
( Crackling)
( Screams)
- ( PanickedScreaming)
- ( Ship Groaning)
( PlanksSplitting)
( EveryoneScreaming)
( Cries Out)
We have to move!
- Give meyour hand, I'll pull you over.
- I can't!
Come on,
give meyour hand!
I've gotyou.
I won't let go.
Come on, I've gotyou.
- What's happening,Jack?
- I don't know. I don't know.
-Jack: Hold on!
- Rose:Jack!
That was close.
Man: Help me, please!
Someone help me, please!
( TerrifiedScreaming,
Thudding)
( Man Yells)
( Panting)
( Lets GoAndScreams)
Woman:
Please help! Help! Help! Help!
( WomanScreamingForHelp )
This is it!
Rose:
Oh, God! Oh, God!
- Hold on!
- Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh!
The ship is going
to suck us down.
Take a deep breath
when I say.
Kickforthe surface
and keep kicking.
Do not let go of my hand.
We're going to make it, Rose.
Trust me.
I trustyou.
Ready? Ready? Now!
( TakingDeep Breath )
( Screaming)
Jack!Jack!
Jack!
-Jack!
- ( EveryoneScreaming)
Jack.Jack!
( Rose's Calls DrownedOut
ByDeafeningScreams)
- ( Gasping)
-Jack!Jack!
No!
-Jack!
- Rose!
Get off her! Get off her!
-Jack!
Swim, Rose!
I need you to swim!
Keep swimming!
- It's so cold!
- Swim, Rose!
Come on... here.
Keep swimming. Come on.
Here, get on it.
Get on top.
( Gasping)
- Come on, Rose.
- ( Gasping)
( Rose Yells)
- Stay on it. Stay on, Rose.
-Jack.
You'll be all right now.
( Whistle Blows)
Crewman:
Return the boats!
- ( Both Shivering)
- ( Whistle Blows)
The boats are coming backfor us, Rose.
Hold onjust a little bit longer.
Crewman:
Return the boats!
They... had to row awayforthe suction,
but now they'll be coming back.
Woman:
Come back!
- For God's sake!
- Please!
- Help us!
( FaintCries ln Distance)
Come back! For God's sake!
You don't understand.
Ifwe go back, they'll swamp the boat.
They'll pull us down, I'm tellingyou.
Knock it off--
You're scaring me.
Come on, girls--
Grab an oar, let's go!
Man: Areyou out ofyour mind? We're
in the middle ofthe North Atlantic!
Now, doyou people want to live
or doyou want to die?
I don't understand a one ofyou.
What's the matterwith you?
It'syour men out there!
- ( Crying)
- There's plenty of room for more.
And there'll be one less on this boat if
you don't shut that hole in yourface!
Woman ( ln Distance):
Come back!
( Whistle Blowing,
People ShoutingForHelp )
Man:
Here, take this one.
Lowe: Now bring in your oars overthere
and tie these two boats together.
Now make sure that's tied up
nice and tight.
Right, listen to me, men,
we have to go back.
I want to transfer all the women
from this boat
into that boat right now
as quick asyou can, please.
Let's get some space there.
Move forward and aft.
( ScatteredMoaning)
( Shivering)
It's getting quiet.
It'sjust going to take them
a couple of minutes
to get the boats organized.
I don't know aboutyou
but I intend to write
a stronglyworded letter
to the White Star Line
about all this.
( ScatteredMoaning
AndPleadingln Distance)
I loveyou,Jack.
Don'tyou do that.
Don'tyou sayyour good-byes.
Notyet.
Doyou understand me?
I'm so cold.
Listen, Rose...
you're going
to get out of here.
You're going to go on
and you're going
to make lots of babies
to watch them grow.
You're going to die an old...
an old ladywarm in her bed.
Not here. Not this night.
Not like this.
Doyou understand me?
I can't feel my body.
Winning that ticket, Rose, was
the best thing that ever happened to me.
It brought me toyou...
and I'm thankful forthat, Rose.
- I'm thankful.
- ( Crying)
You must-- You must--
You must do me this honor--
You must promise me
thatyou'll survive
thatyou won't give up
no matterwhat happens
no matter how hopeless.
Promise me now, Rose
and never let go
ofthat promise.
I promise.
Never let go.
I will never let go,Jack.
( Shivering)
I'll never let go.
- ( Kisses HerHand)
- ( Both Shivering)
Crewman:
Right ahead, sir.
Lowe:
Oars!
Doyou see any moving?
No, sir.
None moving, sir.
Checkthem.
Bring that oar up here.
Checkthem, make sure.
These are dead, sir.
Now give way. Ahead easy.
Careful with your oars.
Don't hit them.
( Shouts):
ls there anyone alive out there?
( FaintAndEchoing):
Can anyone hear me?
Is there anyone alive out there?
We waited too long.
Well, keep checking them,
keep looking!
Is there anyone alive out there?
Can anyone hear me?
( RoseSingingSoftly
AndHaltingly)
( SingingSoftly)
"And it's up she goes. "
" Up she goes. "
( ContinuesSinging)
( Lowe's Voice,
GarbledAndSlow)
Jack?
Jack.
Jack, there's a boat.
Jack?
Jack.
Jack!
( Faltering):
There's a boat,Jack.
Jack?
( CryingSoftly)
( Weakly):
Come back. Come back.
( Voices OfSearchers)
Come back.
( Louder):
Come back, come back.
Hello!
Can anyone hear me?
There's nothing here, sir.
Come back.
I'll never let go.
I promise.
( Sobbing)
( Grunting)
( Blowing Whistle Faintly)
( BlowingStronger)
( Faint Whistling)
- ( Louder Whistling)
- Come about!
( Blowing Whistle Loudly)
( WhistlingReverberates Faintly)
1 ,500 people went into the sea
when Titanicsankfrom under us.
There were 20 boats
floating nearby
and only one came back.
One.
Sixwere saved
from the water
myself included.
Six... out of 1 ,500.
Afterward, the 700 people
in the boats
had nothing to do but wait--
wait to die, wait to live...
wait for an absolution
that would never come.
Oh, sir, I don't thinkyou'll find
any ofyour people down here.
It's all steerage.
Woman:
His hair is reddish brown.
Reddish brown.
Reddish brown and a white beard.
Woman:
lsn't there another passenger list?
- There's no other list.
- Perhaps he's on another ship.
- We're doing all we can, ma'am.
- There's got to be another list!
That's thelasttime
leversawhim.
Hemarried, ofcourse,
andinheritedhis millions
butthe crash of'29
hit his interests hard
andheputapistol
in his mouth thatyear
or so I read.
( Rain Drizzling)
Can I take
your name please, love?
Dawson.
Rose Dawson.
Thankyou.
We neverfound anything onJack.
There's no record of him at all.
No, there wouldn't be,
would there?
And I've never
spoken of him until now.
Not to anyone,
not even your grandfather.
A woman's heart
is a deep ocean ofsecrets.
But nowyou know there was
a man namedJack Dawson
and that he saved me
in everyway
that a person can be saved.
I don't even have
a picture of him.
He exists now only in my memory.
Man: Keldysh, Keldysh, Mir2
on ourwayto the surface.
Brock: You know I was saving this
forwhen I found the diamond.
( Man Givinglnstructions
OverP.A. )
I'm sorry.
Threeyears
I've thought of nothing
except Titanic
but I never got it.
I never let it in.
" Every night in my dreams "
" I seeyou "
" I feel you "
"That is how I know "
"You go on "
" Far across the distance "
"And spaces between us "
"You have come to show "
"You go on "
" Near"
" Far"
"Whereveryou are "
" I believe that "
"The heart does go on "
" Once more "
"You open the door"
"And you're here in my heart "
"And my heart will "
" Go on and on "
" Love can touchjust one time "
"And last for a lifetime "
"And never let go "
"Till we're gone "
" Love was when I loved you "
" One true time I hold to "
" ln my life we'll always "
" Go on "
" Near"
" Far"
"Whereveryou are "
" I believe that "
"The heart does go on "
" Once more "
"You open the door"
"And you're here in my heart "
"And my heart will "
" Go on and on "
"You're here "
"There's nothing I fear"
"And I know that "
" My heart will go on "
"We'll stay"
" Foreverthis way"
"You are safe in my heart "
"And my heart will "
" Go on and on "
( SongEnds)
www.moviesubtitles.org