Juice by Tappy. Juice by Tappy.
Juice by Tappy.
Tappy got juice. Tappy got juice.
Whoa, Tappy.
Juice. Juice. Who wants juice?
Juice.
Juice by you. Juice by you.
Juice. Juice by you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
- We got a winner.
I said, we got a winner.
We got a winner.
Our winner is a flight attendant
from Washington, D.C.
Please welcome Mary Kellington.
Juice by Mary. Juice by Mary.
Juice by Mary.
Harold, please, not again the TV.
Ma. Come on, Ma.
Why you have to make
such a big deal, Ma?
You know you'll get the set back
in a couple of hours.
Why you gotta make me feel
so guilty, Ma?
Jesus. What are you trying to do?
You trying to get me
to break my mother's set?
Or break the radiator?
Maybe blow up the whole house?
Is that what you're trying to do?
Your own flesh and blood, Ma.
Your own son.
Why you always gotta play games
with my head, for chrissake?
Harold, I wouldn't do that.
But the chain isn't for you.
It's for the robbers.
Then why won't you come out?
See what I mean? You see how you
always gotta upset me, Ma?
For chrissake.
Ma?
Ma.
Come on out. Please, Ma?
Screw it.
This isn't happening.
And if it should be happening,
it would be all right.
So don't worry, Seymour.
It'll all work out.
You'll see already.
In the end, it's all nice.
Shit, man.
That motherfucker starting
to look a little seedy, Jim.
What, are you particular
all of a sudden?
Hey, baby, I don't care
if your motherfucker growing hair...
...as long as we get our bread.
- Just give me a hand, Ty.
- All right, man. We're out of here.
Look at that.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Whoopie fuck. The table too.
What do you want from me, huh?
You want me to schlep it on my back?
- You got it, friend.
- I ain't my leopard schlepping. Shit.
Such a son, a goner.
Your mother needs you
like a moose needs a hat rack.
What?
Shit, man.
This is some boss skag, baby.
I mean, dynamite.
Oh, man, it's something else.
You know what we need to do?
We need to get us a piece
of this Brody shit...
...cut it up, and off it.
We could double our money easy.
We could buy us a couple of pieces...
...and we got some whole
another shit going on.
That would be righteous.
I bet in no time at all...
...we could get a pound of pure
straight from Sal the Geep.
That's what I'm talking about, baby.
No hassles.
- How's it going, babe?
- What's up, buddy?
- The usual?
- Yeah, it sounds good.
Jesus Christ.
Anything else?
No. Nothing. I'm all right.
- Good afternoon, Mrs. Goldfarb.
- Good afternoon, Mr. Rabinowitz.
Although I'm not so sure
how good it is.
- And you?
- What can I say?
- You want your TV?
- Yes, if you don't mind.
Mrs. Goldfarb, can I ask you
a question, you won't take it personal?
How many years we know each other?
Who's to count?
Why don't you tell already the police?
Maybe they could talk to Harry?
He wouldn't be stealing
no more the TV.
Mr. Rabinowitz, I couldn't do that.
Harry's my only child.
He's all I have.
Thank you, Mr. Rabinowitz.
Join us in creating excellence. Juice.
You'll have more passion for living
than you ever imagined.
Be excited. Be, be excited.
- Yeah.
- Be excited. Be, be excited.
Change your life. Completely turn it
around. They got the juice?
- Yeah. They got the juice.
- Juice it up.
Hello. Who is it?
- Shit.
- Now what?
It will change your life.
You know how my life started out.
I was an overweight man,
living in a one-room apartment.
I didn't have the money
to feed myself anymore.
I had no will to live.
I'd hit my rock bottom.
I stopped right there. In 30 days...
- Hello?
- Mrs. Goldfarb? Mrs. Sara Goldfarb?
Me, speaking.
Mrs. Goldfarb, this is Lyle Russel
from Malin & Block.
- I'm not interested.
- Wait, Mrs. Goldfarb.
I'm not selling anything. Nothing.
I just want to offer you a chance...
...to be on television.
- You see, Malin & Block...
- Television?
That's right, Mrs. Goldfarb.
Television. Congratulations.
- Look, I don't have any...
- I'm not looking for money.
I'm calling to tell you
you've already won.
Malin & Block discovers contestants
for most of America's television shows.
You've already been chosen
from a long list...
...of potential contestants,
meaning you've already won.
Yes, Mrs. Goldfarb.
I never thought I'd be on television.
I'm just a...
That's right. You, on television.
We'll be sending you all
the necessary information in the mail.
Goodbye, congratulations,
and take care.
Juice my life.
But I don't get it.
Why are you so hard on your folks?
I mean, they give you everything.
They hook you up with an apartment,
with a croaker shrink.
Which is fine, you know. It's great.
It's just money is never
what I really wanted from them.
You know?
That's pretty much all I have to give.
Why don't you get away from them?
How am I gonna do that?
I don't know.
What about your clothes?
Your sketches are great.
Open up a store.
I can't.
Why not?
Then when will I have time
to hang with you?
Well.
So where's the party?
When I tell you,
you're gonna jump out of the window.
This is a tough one.
I got a great diet book.
Hey.
They're coming.
Be excited. Be, be excited.
- Thanks for the tip.
Thank you.
It was commitment, it was passion,
it was three things.
Three things that I did. Three things
that I found could change my life.
I thought I'd catch a little sun today.
Really? Well, in a box, you'll catch it.
Why don't you just relax...
...and think how gorgeous you'll look
with your new red hair, huh?
Today the hair, tomorrow the sun.
Anybody want to waste some time?
Angel says this is the time.
We should do it now.
- Shit, I'm gonna call Brody tomorrow.
- Who's Brody?
That's my sweet connection.
He's got some unbelievable shit.
Shit, righteous.
Look, Marion, we got this idea.
What is it?
If we get a piece of this stuff, we can
cut it up and double our money.
Shit, man, then we get us
a pound of pure and retire.
Now, you know what that means.
Homeboy has it.
We can get off hard knocks,
and be on easy street.
Shit.
What's the catch?
That's a red. I mean, that's a red.
I mean, it's not a red red,
but that's a red. It's a red.
- Red?
- Yeah. It's a red.
- You're telling me that's red?
- Yeah, I'm telling you. It's a red.
Then what's orange?
If this is a red,
I want to know, what's orange?
Well, it could be...
...that it's a little orange too.
I need to know something.
I always thought you were
the most beautiful girl I ever seen.
Really?
Ever since I first saw you.
That's nice, Harry.
That makes me feel really good.
You know that other people
have told me that before.
And it was meaningless.
Why?
Because you thought
they were pulling your leg?
No, no, not like that.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know or even care if they were.
It's just, from them, it was...
...just meaningless.
You know?
But you say it, and I hear it.
I really hear it.
You know, somebody like you could
really make things all right for me.
You think?
What is that?
Remember when I told you
about the store?
Yeah.
Well, I been thinking about it a lot...
...and I put together some numbers...
...and it's not impossible.
I mean, you know, you could do it.
You should do it.
I mean, we could do it together.
What do you think?
Stop already.
You'll feel better in the red dress
than in a cheese Danish.
Three things is all I did
to change my life. Three things.
- Number one.
- No red meat.
Think about it. What do they stick
in red meat? I ate red meat.
I ate red meat to the point
where I would eat it slab right off raw.
Loved my meat. I turned it around.
You need to be committed.
You need to be passionate.
No red meat.
No red meat for 30 days.
No red meat. You guys are terrific.
Three things is all I did
to change my life. Three things.
- Ada told us. It's gorgeous.
- Sara.
- We're gonna make it darker tomorrow.
- Why darker?
- To go with my red dress.
- But now it's looking like Madonna.
This is not Madonna.
And neither is this,
but soon I'm going on a diet.
- What diet are you on?
- Eggs and grapefruit.
- Oh, I was on that one. Lots of luck.
- It's not so bad.
- How long you been on it?
- All day.
All day? It's 1 :00. All day.
- I'm thinking thin.
- She's thinking thin.
My Louise,
she lost 50 pounds just like that.
- Like that?
- Like what?
What did you do,
put her in a sweatbox?
No. She went to a doctor,
and he gave her pills.
- You don't want to eat.
- So? What's so good about that?
I'm sitting here not thinking about
chopped liver and pastrami on rye?
You really shouldn't talk like that
when someone's on a diet.
Oh, big deal.
I'll sneak another wedge of grapefruit.
- I'm thinking thin.
- Oh, Sara, the mailman.
Sara Goldfarb? You have
something for Sara Goldfarb?
- I'm expecting something.
- Ms. Goldfarb. Goldfarb.
- Sara Goldfarb.
- This is it?
- That's it. It's here.
- Wait, wait. I gotta get my stuff.
- All right.
- Okay, I got the tape.
Your name. What's your name?
Put down your name.
S-A-R-A...
...G-O-L-D...
... F-A-R-B.
Dynamite?
Dynamite.
All right, we on our way. All right.
Brody's man said he got
some real fine shit, man.
All right, man.
Should be cool.
Hey, Ty?
- Let's do this right, man.
- Come on, baby. Naturally.
- Come on.
- Hurry, hurry. Let's hurry.
- I wonder when you'll hear.
- Yeah, me too.
- Hi.
- I want to come with you.
You know, maybe they'll send you
to Tavern on the Green.
That's where they send all those stars.
Yeah, I'm eating eggs and grapefruit
at Tavern on the Green.
I hope they have that.
- Hurry before the mailman comes.
- Here we are.
- Oh, God.
- Mail it.
Oh, it's done.
Oh, this is so exciting.
This is so exciting.
There it is, Jim.
There it is, baby.
Oh, shit.
Should we try?
Wait, Ty.
Look.
This is our chance to make it big.
We play it right...
...and we can get a pound of pure.
But if we get wasted...
...we'll fuck it up.
Right on.
Hey, look, I ain't trying to jive you, Jim.
I don't want to be running the streets
with my sneakers ripped up...
...and my nose running down
to my chin.
All I'm saying
is we should take a little taste...
...so we know how much to cut.
It's business.
Fair enough.
Shit.
Thank you. Three things is all I did
to change my life.
Thirty days is all it takes.
Three things.
- Number two.
No refined sugar.
Sugar's everywhere in sight.
Sugar's everywhere.
You know they even put sugar
in bottled water?
I was sick with sugar.
That was my medicine.
It nurtured me.
It nurtured my spiraling brain
that felt I was a loser.
- Juice by you.
- Number two is no refined sugar.
- No refined sugar.
Sodas? Don't even think
about sodas anymore.
No sucking candies. Very good, sir.
None of that stuff. Stay away from it.
Check loaves of bread. Watch your
toothpaste. No refined sugar.
I said, "For 30 days,
I'm gonna eat right.
I am gonna pick up my spirits...
...and I am gonna try."
I found hope.
And in that hope,
I found a way of thinking.
Shut up.
- Hello?
- Rosie?
- Yeah?
- Sara.
Yeah?
I need the number of that doctor.
I don't understand
why you gotta see him.
Cut the son of a bitch loose,
for chrissake.
Because I don't want him...
... mentioning to my parents
that I've stopped therapy.
They're already so pissed off at me,
they're thinking of cutting me off.
Harry, I'm not gonna sleep with him
or anything.
I'm gonna come home
after the concert.
You're jealous.
Harry's jealous?
Oh, put your arms around me.
- No.
- Oh, you are so stubborn.
Put your arms around me.
Stop that.
I'll suck your eyeballs out.
Well?
I'm disappointed
that you're indisposed.
Is Anita out of town or something?
Why do you ask?
I was just wondering
if she was indisposed.
No. She's fine, thank you.
Actually, she's in Florida.
Can I ask something
personal, Arnold?
Of course.
- Well.
- Anything. What?
l... You just have
something over here.
- It's gone?
- A little bit. Little bit lower.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
It's much better. It's... Arnold.
So how are you, Mrs. Goldfarb?
How am l? Enormous.
- That's why I'm here.
- Oh, I've seen much worse.
Thank you.
How's your hearing and vision?
I have both.
The doctor will be with you shortly.
I see you're a little overweight.
A little? I have 50 pounds
I'm willing to donate.
We can take care of that.
No problem.
We're on our way, baby.
Baby, we're on our way.
God, it's great out there.
I mean, everybody is thirsty.
Come to me.
Harry.
I am so glad.
Naturally.
Purple in the morning...
... blue in the afternoon...
...orange in the evening.
There's my three meals,
Mr. Smarty-Pants.
And green at night.
Just like that. One, two, three, four.
Why don't you come back
to bed, baby?
Come on now, Alice.
Got plenty of time for that.
Right now I'm grooving
with these new mirrors I got.
I told you, Mom. One day I'd make it.
You don't have to make anything,
my sweet.
You just have to love
your mama, huh?
What you doing, baby?
Nothing.
Just thinking about you.
And all the nasty things
I'm about to do to you.
Get over here.
Ty, you scare me sometimes.
Oh, now, I don't want to scare you.
Shit, I don't want to scare nobody.
All I want out of life is a little bit
of peace and happiness, that's all.
Right now...
... I'm with the finest fox
I ever laid my eyes on.
That's what I'll do.
For my mother, you know?
I been thinking about getting
something for her, you know, like...
Like a present or something.
But I didn't know
what I was gonna get.
- Until now.
- And?
I finally asked myself, right?
What's her fix?
Television, right?
I mean, if ever there's a TV junkie,
it's the old lady.
I figure I owe her a set anyway
with all the wear and tear it got...
...from being schlepped back and forth
to old Abe's all the time.
You really love her, don't you?
I guess so, you know?
Most of the time,
I just want her to be happy.
Let's go get it now.
Well, let's push off first.
It's early, Harry.
We shouldn't get going till tonight.
Be excited. Be, be excited.
Be excited.
You need to be committed.
You need to be passionate.
I am a living testament.
Sixty-five pounds thinner. I feel great.
Juice.
- Number three.
Whoa, number three.
This drives most people crazy.
This is easy so far...
...but give yourself the 30 days.
I guarantee you ...
I mean, that is thin.
- She doesn't look the same.
- This is a waistline.
I can almost zip the dress.
The red dress?
- I've almost got the zipper up.
- Oh, Sara. The mailman.
When I see it,
I'm gonna wave it all over the place.
- Are you sure you looked?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
What did he say?
Don't worry, Sara. It'll come.
- He said it'll come.
- Yeah, don't worry.
- Two months for a package.
- Two months?
- It's Harry.
- Oh, look.
- Harry.
- Hey, Ma, easy.
You're gonna crush me,
for chrissakes.
Come inside.
- Hello.
- Hi, Harry.
- Hello, Harry.
- We'll have a little visit.
So how are you, Harry?
You're looking so good.
- You want something to eat?
- No, Ma.
A little nosh maybe? A piece of cake?
I could go out and get something
if you want.
I don't have anything in the house,
but Ada would have something.
A cupcake maybe?
You want something to eat?
No, no, Ma. Nothing. Please, sit.
You're making me dizzy, for chrissake.
Yeah. You notice anything
about me, huh?
You notice I'm slimmer?
- Yeah, I guess you are, Ma.
- Twenty-five pounds I lost.
Twenty-five pounds.
Can you believe it?
- And that's only the beginning.
- Great, Ma. That's really great.
I'm really happy for you,
but will you sit? Please.
Sorry I haven't been around in a while,
Ma, but I been busy. Real busy.
Oh, yeah? You got a good job?
You're doing real well?
- Yeah, real good. Real good.
- What kind of business?
Well, I'm sort of a distributor,
like, for a big importer.
- Hey, Ma.
- Oh, I'm so happy for you.
Easy. You're killing me.
Jesus, what,
have you been lifting weights?
- I always knew you could do that.
- You were right.
Now maybe you'll meet a nice girl
and have a baby?
Well, I already met one.
Ma. Ma, Ma, Ma,
don't go ape shit, all right?
So who is she?
Who's her parents?
- What do they do?
- You know her. Marion.
Marion Silver? Remember?
- Oh, Silver.
- Remember? Yeah.
Of course. Manhattan Beach.
He's got a house on the Esplanade.
Garment business.
Yeah. He's real big
in women's undies.
Hey, hey, before you go bouncing all
over again, and make me forget, Ma...
Just...
What I want to tell you is that...
...well, I got you a present.
Oh, Harry, I don't need a present.
Just have a baby.
Will you let me tell you what I got you?
Will you, Ma?
Christ, you are really something else
today, you know that?
Look, I know...
Well...
I'm sorry for being such a bastard.
I want to make it up.
I mean, I know I can't change
anything that's happened...
... but I want you to know that...
That I love you...
...and that I'm sorry.
And I want you to be happy.
So I got you a brand-new TV set.
It's gonna be delivered in
a couple of days. It's from Macy's.
Yeah.
Your father would be so happy...
... if he could see what you're doing
for your mother.
See that, Seymour?
You see how good your son is?
He knows what it's like for his mother,
living all alone.
No one to visit her.
Hey, Ma?
- You on uppers?
- What?
You're on uppers?
- You're on diet pills, ain't you?
- I told you. I'm going to a specialist.
That's what I thought.
You making a croaker for speed,
ain't you?
Harry, are you all right?
I'm going to a doctor.
- What does he give you, Ma? Pills?
- Of course he gives me pills.
What kind of pills?
A purple one, a blue one,
an orange one.
I mean, like, what's in them?
Harry, I'm Sara Goldfarb,
not Albert Einstein.
How should I know?
Does the stuff make you feel good,
sort of, and give you lots of pep?
Well, yeah, a little.
A little? I can hear you grinding
your teeth from here.
That goes away at night.
- At night?
- Yeah, when I take the green one.
Thirty minutes, I'm asleep.
Poof, just like that.
Ma, Ma.
You gotta cut that stuff loose.
- I'm telling you, it's no good.
- What do you mean, no good?
Twenty-five pounds I've lost.
Big deal. So what? You want
to be a dope fiend, for chrissake?
What is with the dope fiend? Am l
foaming at the mouth or something?
He's a nice doctor.
I am telling you,
that croaker's no good.
How come you know so much, huh?
How come you know more
about medicine than a doctor?
Believe me, Ma, I know.
All right?
You'll get strung out, for chrissake.
Come on. I almost fit in my red dress.
The one I wore
to your high-school graduation?
The one your father liked so much.
Oh, I remember how he looked at me
in that red dress.
Mama, what is the big deal
about the red dress?
I'm gonna wear it...
You don't know.
I'm gonna be on television.
I got a call and an application, and...
Come on, Ma. Who's pulling your leg?
No, no, no, I'm telling you.
I'm gonna be a contestant
on television. I don't know when yet.
They haven't told me when,
but you'll see how proud you are...
...when you see your mother
in a red dress...
...on television in golden shoes.
What is the big deal
about being on television?
Those pills you're taking will kill you
before you ever get on.
Big deal?
You drove up in a cab.
Did you see who had the best seat?
I'm somebody now, Harry.
Everybody likes me.
Soon, millions of people will see me...
...and they'll all like me.
I'll tell them about you...
...and your father.
How good he was to us.
Remember?
It's a reason to get up in the morning.
It's a reason to lose weight...
...to fit in the red dress.
It's a reason to smile.
lt makes tomorrow all right.
What have I got, Harry?
Why should I even make the bed
or wash the dishes?
I do them, but why should l?
I'm alone.
Your father's gone.
You're gone.
I got no one to...
...care for.
What have I got, Harry?
I'm lonely.
I'm old.
You got friends, Ma.
It's not the same.
They don't need me.
I like the way I feel.
I like thinking about the red dress...
...and the television
and you and your father.
Now when I get the sun, I smile.
I'll come and visit, Ma.
You know, now that I'm straight,
my business is going good...
... I'll come, me and Marion.
We'll come for dinner.
Yeah, good. You bring her.
I'll make a mushroom soup
and a roast.
That sounds great, Ma.
That sounds great.
I'll give you a call ahead of time,
all right?
Okay.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you have a nice girl
and your own business.
I'm glad.
I gotta go, Ma.
I got an appointment in Manhattan
in a little bit, but...
- But I'll be back.
- Okay. You've still got your key?
Yeah, I got it, Ma.
Bye, son.
Brody says you coming up quick, kid.
Thanks, man.
He says you're smart, you're loyal,
and you're not a junkie.
Brody wants to promote you.
He wants to give you more
responsibility. You interested?
Yeah. Yeah. Shit, yeah, man.
Fuck me, I'll kill you.
- Brody says, you fuck him, I kill you.
- I got that.
Remember that.
Shit, you got a white driver.
Fuck.
What the fuck.
Don't move.
I love you, Harry.
You make me feel like a person.
Like I'm me.
And I'm beautiful.
You are beautiful.
You're the most beautiful girl
in the world.
You're my dream.
No, Mrs. Goldfarb. I'm absolutely
certain. I've checked again.
But maybe you gave me a weaker one
last time.
That isn't possible, Mrs. Goldfarb.
Like I said before,
they're all the same potency.
- But something isn't the same.
- You're becoming adjusted to them.
It's nothing to worry about,
Mrs. Goldfarb, okay?
We got a winner.
- We got a winner.
She's a beautiful woman
with a winning sense of humor...
...and a magical smile straight
from Brighton Beach, Brooklyn.
Let's give a juicy welcome
to Mrs. Sara Goldfarb.
Juice by Sara. Juice by Sara.
Juice by Sara. Whoa, Sara got juice.
Sara got juice. Whoa, Sara.
Love. Love, Tyrone C.
Get your shit together. You made bail.
How much?
They got most of our cash,
and you're up for consorting.
Oh, shit, man.
Angel says there's a war
between the Italians and the blacks.
He says Sal the Geep
is keeping his shit down in Florida...
- ... until guys like Brody are knocked off.
- Shit.
- No one's got a thing.
- Except Big Tim.
Well, shit, let's go see him.
He ain't selling.
He only give it up for pussy.
- What?
- Pussy.
He's hooked on the thing, man.
I told him I'd give him all he wants.
He said I ain't cute enough for him.
Come on, number three.
Most people.
You're gonna like it.
This is easy.
In thirty days, it will. I gua...
You all right?
Yeah. lt was just a bad dream.
Want some water?
- Maybe we should dip in now.
- Come on, Marion.
I already told you, all right?
It's all we have.
Tyrone is gonna score in the morning,
Harry.
I don't know. It's... It's a bitch out there.
It'll be okay.
It'll be okay, Harry.
Yeah.
I guess so.
I love you, Harry.
What seems to be the problem?
Your weight's doing fine.
The weight's fine. I'm not.
The refrigerator.
Is something wrong?
Everything's...
asfasf
a
fasfsa
afs
- Confused.
- That's nothing to worry about.
Just get this filled.
Make an appointment for a week.
Well?
Ty ain't found nothing yet.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Well, you have to do
something, Harry.
It's your fault
that we don't have something.
What are you talking about?
You were all hot in the biscuit
to get off last night.
- That is such bullshit.
- You didn't have to.
- We could've had something.
- What was I to do?
I'm gonna sit around and watch you
push off and not go myself?
Just don't put it all on me, okay?
Don't worry, man.
We'll fill it up again.
You know, things will get better.
And then we'll be filling the box
back up, you know?
So you want to hear the news?
What news?
Well, you got your good news,
you got your bad news.
Shoot.
The good news is, a couple of days...
...there's gonna be some prime
back on the street.
Really?
Who told you that?
- Angel.
- Yeah?
Yeah, he said, Sal the Geep
sent word...
...to let a couple of keys
go for the season.
Him being a good Christian
and all...
...and he don't mind feeding
during the glorious season.
- You believe it?
- Well, I did.
Until I heard the bad news.
Yeah?
The price is double.
You're gonna have to cop for weight.
At least a half a piece.
How much?
- Two.
- Two?
- That's fucking insane.
- Hey, what the fuck you gonna do?
Man ain't gonna lay no nickel bag
on you, that's for sure.
Where are we gonna get two?
You mean Arnold?
Well, your parents won't even return
your call.
I haven't seen him in months.
So what, he's still calling, ain't he?
I don't know.
Look, I don't know what else to do.
Okay, this is our last chance
to get back on track.
We won't have to scuffle and make
the freezing scene every day.
We need the bread.
Getting the money
is not the problem, Harry.
Well, what is the problem,
for chrissake?
I don't know what I'm gonna have to do
to get it.
Look.
Baby.
We'll be back in business in no time.
We'll start moving again.
We'll start saving.
It'll be perfect, just like it was.
I promise, Marion.
You'll see.
No, I'm just...
I've had this flu forever it seems like.
Are you depressed?
No. It's nothing like that.
I've been...
I've been really busy.
Actually, I've been designing nonstop.
That's wonderful.
Glad to hear you've been productive.
To be perfectly frank...
... I was a little surprised
to hear from you.
Is there something wrong?
No. Why?
Well, it's usually the case...
...when you get a call from someone
you haven't heard from for a while.
Everything's fine.
Actually.
I have a favor to ask.
You smug fuck.
What is it?
- I need to borrow some money.
- May I ask what for?
Can you turn the light off?
What do you want the light off for?
I just do.
- You never did before.
- Please, Arnold.
For that special someone in your life.
I had these, which I got for my wife...
...and she loves it. And all her friends
are always wanting to see it.
And you know, when they hold it,
they're amazed at how heavy it is.
It's really got some nice...
What you've always wanted.
A genuine, hand-crafted
Sapphire and diamond ring.
And you're gonna really
love the original.
You'll want to buy one
for all of your friends.
The holidays are coming
right around the corner.
You need to make some decisions
soon before they're all gone.
Sapphire is my wife's birthstone.
- Where is everybody?
- I don't know, man.
All Angel said was
meet at Walbaron's.
- You sure this is the right Walbaron's?
- Yeah, man. I'm positive. All right?
Look, will you just watch my back?
And I'll watch yours, all right?
What the fuck are we supposed
to do now?
Hey.
- Everyone and their mother.
- The truck's gonna be here soon.
Yeah, the truck's gonna be here.
Back up.
You ain't gotta be putting up a front.
Gun! Gun!
Stupid fucking junkie, man.
We're fucked.
- Them motherfuckers is going back.
- That was the last shit.
Sitting their ass in that sun
while we sit here ass deep...
... in some motherfucking snow.
Hey.
What would happen
if we went down there to cop?
- Are you serious?
- Why not?
What the fuck are you saying?
We supposed to walk up to some clerk
at a hotel and ask him for a connection?
Get with it. You telling me that you can't
nose out some dope when it's around?
Man, we got nothing to lose.
It's wide open,
and if we get there right away...
...we can name our own price,
and we can sit back...
...and have those fucking fools
scuffle the streets for us.
Yeah, man.
Last summer was
a motherfucking ball, huh, Jim?
Yeah.
lt just seems like a thousand years
ago since last summer, man.
It'll be like that again, man.
I can get Angel to get us a short...
... if we promise him
some dynamite skag.
Baby.
Where have you been?
- Where the hell you think I been?
- Waiting all day for you.
Where's the score?
Well, we had a little bit of a problem.
You see,
I mean, everything was going good...
...and then some dumb-ass junkie...
Did what?
Some dumb-ass junkie did what?
You mean, you fucked it up?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You promised me that everything
was gonna be okay.
I fucked that sleazebag for you, and l
put myself through fucking hell for you.
- There's nothing out there.
- I don't give a shit.
You fucking loser.
You want to be sure
we have some extra stuff?
Ty told me about a guy
who's holding some weight.
But he ain't selling it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, Ty. Give me that guy's number.
- What guy?
- The guy who likes broads.
Big Tim? For what?
- Just give me the fucking number.
- All right.
934-8777.
You worry so goddamn much, here,
go fix yourself up with him.
You won't have to
fucking wait around...
...and I won't have to freeze my ass off
in the fucking streets.
Fuck you.
- All right. We got a winner.
- We got a winner.
- Oh, we got a winner.
She's a beautiful woman
with a winning sense of humor...
...and a magical smile.
She's really gonna win your heart.
Straight from Brighton Beach,
Brooklyn ...
...please give a juicy welcome
to our very own Mrs. Sara Goldfarb.
Juice by Sara. Juice by Sara.
Juice by Sara. Whoa, Sara.
Whoa, Sara.
- It's a pleasure to be here.
- It's a pleasure to have you.
And that is one smashing dress
you have on.
Okay, Tappy, if you don't mind,
I would just like to say hello...
...to my husband Seymour...
...and to my beautiful, successful son,
Harry.
I hope you're in love.
Please come and see me.
And bring Marion, won't you?
I'm sure he'll be here soon.
It's almost that time. Are you ready?
I'm ready, Tappy.
Not to worry. Not to worry.
- Thirty days to revolutionize your life.
- What are you doing there?
- Why are you here?
- Join us in creating the excitement.
What do you want?
- Oh, Tappy.
- Juice. Join us in creating excellent...
I thought you'd never ask.
Oh, my God.
Look at this.
It's disgusting.
Well, what do you expect?
Could you do any better?
- Look at this. It's cracking.
- It's an old building.
lt hasn't been painted in years.
I'm old. Alone.
You don't understand.
Please. I'll explain.
What is it? What is it?
No, I don't want that.
What are you doing?
Get away from me.
- Ready, Mrs. Goldfarb.
- Ready for what?
Three, two...
What? What am I supposed to do?
I don't know what to...
Feed me, Sara.
Feed me Sara.
- Feed me, Sara.
- Feed me.
Feed me, Sara.
Feed me, Sara. Feed me, Sara.
Thank you, Angel.
I sure hope this motherfucker works,
man.
My ass could use some heat. How
long you think this trip gonna take?
We'll make it in a day, no problem.
- A day?
- Yeah.
Shit. California, here we come.
It's Florida, Ty. Florida.
Shit, man. California, Florida.
Either way,
your pale ass getting a tan, man.
Do you know if this train goes
to Madison Avenue?
Do you know Malin & Block?
I have their address.
It's on Madison Avenue.
- I'm gonna be on television.
- You're a wack.
Hey, hey.
Hello? Do you know if this train
Goes to Madison Avenue?
I'm gonna be on television.
I just have to find out when.
Florida.
Oh, when is he gonna be back?
A few days.
Angel, what am I supposed to do?
Angel, you gotta help me.
Oh, come on. I can get you money.
Angel, there's gotta be something.
Anything. Help me.
Why aren't you calling me?
I have to know when I'm gonna be
on television.
I'm Sara Goldfarb.
And you should tell me
when I'm gonna be on television.
Just sit for a moment. I'll ring them.
I just wanna know when.
Maybe you lost my card.
Please, darling. You'll have a look,
and you'll tell me.
It's not the prizes.
I'll give them away.
I just want to be on the show.
I've waited so long...
...to be on with my Harry...
...and my grandson.
Here, Mrs. Goldfarb. Sip this.
Sometimes it takes a while
to get called for a show, Mrs. Goldfarb.
- Is this her?
- Yes.
- Can you walk?
- I'm walking across the stage.
And you should see my Harry
on television.
We're giving the prizes away.
I just wanted to be on the show.
- What's her name?
- We think it's Sara Goldfarb.
Call Seymour.
And tell him to meet me
at the beauty parlor.
I got the red dress that I wore
to Harry's graduation...
...and the gold shoes.
Okay, Mrs. Goldfarb. Here we go.
One, two, three.
Let's take it nice and easy.
Yeah?
Hi.
Harold, I'm going to be on television.
Oh, shit.
Goddamn, Jimmy.
How long you had that?
Just a few days.
That shit don't look too good.
Yeah, it don't feel
too good either, man.
But a little stuff will take care of that.
Hey, hey, What's wrong with you?
Don't shoot in there.
I'll blow it if I don't.
Fuck it.
Shit.
- He's gonna be surprised.
- Hi, how are you? Can you hear me?
- Yeah, Seymour.
- Did you take anything?
I took my red dress, and...
- No emergency. Take her to Psych.
- Television.
Come on in.
Thanks.
What's your name?
Marion.
Well, what do you know.
Maid Marion.
I'm Little John.
- You have a beautiful view.
- Know what I like about paddy chicks?
They give good head.
Now, black broads don't know nothing
about no head.
I don't know why.
Maybe it has something to do
with some ancient tribal customs.
Come here.
Better save some of that energy.
Come on.
Oh, I know it's pretty, baby.
But I didn't take it out for air.
Yeah.
I told your ass,
stay away from that arm. See?
I gotta call Marion, man.
That's about
to be a long distance call now.
That's 600 miles.
Man, we are 600 miles
closer to Miami.
Yeah, it's also 600 miles further away
from New York, Ty.
I know where you can pick up
a real nice taste.
Though it's more like play.
Sunday night?
We're throwing a little gathering.
All good people.
No. I can't. I'm busy.
Anyway, I'm not really hooked.
Oh, I know.
But it's a real nice taste.
I'll see you Sunday, Maid Marion.
Mrs. Goldfarb. Just try
and answer my questions, okay?
When did you start taking the pills?
- The summer.
- You started in the summer.
- Last summer?
- I got the best place in the sun.
- Okay.
- Ada fixed my hair.
Everything is gonna be all right.
We'll get you fixed up in no time.
- Hold tight, man. Hold tight.
- I can't cut it, man. I can't cut it.
I gotta do something
about this arm, Ty.
All right.
Let me see what it looks like, man.
Oh, damn, Jim.
- Oh, man.
- That's the ugliest motherfucker...
... I ever seen.
- I gotta call Marion.
- Fuck that.
We gotta get you to a hospital, man.
What is that?
I don't want that. I don't want that.
God.
What's the problem?
It's my arm. My arm is killing me.
Let's have a look at it.
All right.
I'll be back in a minute.
I want to just play Blackjack all night
long. So I make up this routine.
I tell them,
"You guys go. I don't feel good.
You guys go and have a good time."
Sure enough, they leave the room.
- Ready. One, two, three.
- Two, three.
And then, as soon as they leave...
... I go running back down to the casino,
sit at my Blackjack table, man.
I am there for the whole night.
Finally, I get up so big...
... I've got $500 black chips
in my pocket.
I swear to God.
The hours are going by, I'm laying
back, I'm hitting on hard 17s.
lt was beautiful.
Next thing I know,
this guy is sitting next to me.
He's a security guard.
He's telling me I have to leave...
...like it's a nice conversation. I'm like,
"Why are you telling me to leave?"
He says, "You have to because you've
been betting with the man next to you."
- And then...
- Swallow.
Swallow.
The guy is forcing me out of the room.
Rob Smart to Kid Care.
Rob Smart to Kid Care, please.
You have to eat, Mrs. Goldfarb.
If we're gonna get you healthy,
you have to eat. Okay?
Work with the attendants. I'm gonna try
new medications. They should help.
Hello?
Marion?
Harry?
Marion, I've been thinking about you
so much.
Are you okay?
When are you coming home?
Soon.
When?
- You're holding out, right?
- Harry?
Can you come today?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'll come.
I'll come today.
You just wait for me, all right?
- Okay, Harry.
- I'm coming back, Marion.
- Yeah.
- Marion?
Yeah?
I'm really sorry, Marion.
I know.
Mrs. Goldfarb?
You all right?
So, Mrs. Goldfarb,
we've tried several medications...
...and you don't seem
to be responding.
I believe we might be at a point...
...where we might want to try
some alternative methods.
We've had excellent results
with ECT in the past.
So if I can just get
your John Hancock...
...we'll get underway.
Great. Thanks.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- Somebody help us.
- I need a doctor, man.
- My friend is sick.
- I need some help, please. Help us.
- I can't take it, man. My arm.
- My fucking arm.
- Just hang in fucking tight.
- Oh, man!
- Help us!
Somebody fucking help us, please!
Maid Marion.
Welcome.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir.
Okay for work.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir.
Okay for work.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir.
Okay for work.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir.
Okay for work. Can you hear me?
Can you see me?
- Yes, sir.
- Okay for work.
- Fellows, meet Marion.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
Okay for work.
- Yes, sir.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
Okay for work.
- Showtime.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes.
Say sir. Goddamn New York,
dope-fiend niggers.
Learn some manners.
Can you hear me? Can you see me?
- Yes, sir.
- Okay for work.
- Mouthpiece.
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?
Says he's got something wrong
with his arm.
I don't think he'll be putting dope
in that arm.
Smells worse than he do.
Test.
Get him to the hospital.
I don't expect he'll live out the week.
Ready, and one.
That's the trouble
with you New York dope fiends.
You got a rotten attitude,
you know that, man?
- So what are we gonna do now?
- Ass to ass.
Ass to ass.
Put your spineless back into it.
Come on.
Ready, and two.
Ass to ass.
Put it in there.
That's it.
- Nice and easy.
- Keep it in.
That's the way.
Lose the clothes. I need one gram.
Don't give up. Don't give up.
Move it. Move it. Move it.
Okay. Ready, and three.
Come, come, come.
We're gonna take it off at the shoulder.
Let's move it, people.
Come, come, come.
Marion!
Marion?
It's all right.
Don't worry. You're in a hospital.
- Marion?
- Who's that?
She'll be sent for. She'll come.
No.
No?
No, she won't.
She'll come.
- All right. We got a winner.
- We got a winner.
Our next winner
is that delightful personality...
...straight
from Brighton Beach, Brooklyn.
Please give a juicy welcome
to Mrs. Sara Goldfarb.
I'm delighted to tell you that you have
just won the grand prize.
Oh, no.
Let me tell you what you've won.
Your prize has a sweet smile
and his own private business.
He just got engaged and is about
to get married this summer.
Will you please give a warm
and juicy welcome.
Harry Goldfarb.
Juice by Harry. Juice by Harry.
Juice by Harry. Whoa, Harry.
Harry got juice. Harry got juice.
Whoa, Harry.
I love you, Harry.
I love you, too, Ma.